<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<data-set>
	<project ID="230526388">
		<Name>Ricardo</Name>
		<Surname>da Cruz e Sousa</Surname>
		<Affiliation>other</Affiliation>
		<City_of_Institution>Rio de Janeiro</City_of_Institution>
		<country_001>Brazil</country_001>
		<title_of_project>Climate Risks and Adaptation Solutions in Copacabana</title_of_project>
		<credits_for_project>Ricardo da Cruz e Sousa, Universidade Federal do Rio de Janeiro</credits_for_project>
		<year_of_project>2022</year_of_project>
		<description_of_project>This video is intended to be used as a communication tool on climate change to increase public awareness and perception of adaptation risks and solutions in Copacabana in Rio de Janeiro. Copacabana has the densest coastal urbanization in Brazil, which, combined with an aging and inefficient infrastructure, increases the populations exposure and vulnerability to climate risks. Through visual representation and a narrative, this approach to landscape design generates new knowledge and communicates it visually to elicit emotional responses, interest, debate, behavioral change and climate action.</description_of_project>
		<synopsis_of_project>"Climate adaptation is mandatory and urgent, particularly for low-lying coastal urbanizations."</synopsis_of_project>
		<keywords_of_project>Adaptation, climate change, Copacabana, landscape, risks.</keywords_of_project>
		<duration_of_solution>long</duration_of_solution>
		<primary_SDG>Climate Action</primary_SDG>
		<secondary_SDG>          Reduced Inequality, Sustainable Cities and Communities,   Life Below Water,   </secondary_SDG>
		<country_of_contribution>Brazil</country_of_contribution>
		<city_of_contribution>Rio de Janeiro</city_of_contribution>
		<lat>-22.969759</lat>
		<long>-43.186379</long>
		<climate_hazard>meteorological climatological Hydrological geophysical</climate_hazard>
		<project_ID>230526388</project_ID>
		<no_of_images>3</no_of_images>
		<category_of_contribution>solutions_to_adapt_to_climate_</category_of_contribution>
		<extra_links>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=NXHLwBvwBm8</extra_links>
	</project>
	<project ID="230585066">
		<Name>Sina</Name>
		<Surname>Hensel</Surname>
		<Affiliation>rwth_aachen__germany</Affiliation>
		<City_of_Institution>Aachen</City_of_Institution>
		<country_001>Germany</country_001>
		<title_of_project>SUNBURN</title_of_project>
		<credits_for_project>Sina Hensel, director, cinematography, editing
(Sina Hensel is a visual artist and researcher based in Brussels)
Rosa Whiteley, director, cinematography, editing
(Rosa Whiteley is an architectural researcher based in London)
Simonluca Laitempergher, sound production
PACT Zollverein, production</credits_for_project>
		<year_of_project>2021</year_of_project>
		<description_of_project>Sunscreens are no longer just applied to our skins, but also to the skins of mountains, clouds, or trees. As we struggle to control shifting climates and our ability to adapt to them, sun screening has grown in size, through solar geoengineering, to encompass the planet. Skins in different bodies - cells, species, ecologies, territories and technologies - often change colour in a reaction to UV light. Chemical alarms in cells trigger inflammation and metabolic mechanisms produce protective pigments. Leaves flash red, algae secrete pink, whilst humans smear shades of white. As climate related stress amplifies, colours strain to perform resistance. These colours act as both a defence and a signal for the intensity of the sun; bearing the impressions of the weather-world. SUNBURN explores the spaces between colourful feral ecologies, and synthetic post-human skins; uncovering methods of living in a hotter, sun- scorched earth. Whilst sun screening occurs differently in different species, from whales to trees, this film explores four methods and acts of sun screening; Spraying, Secreting, Smearing or Costuming.</description_of_project>
		<synopsis_of_project>To accomplish agency through the senses.</synopsis_of_project>
		<keywords_of_project>UV-Radiation, (Skin)Care, Sunscreen, Shifting Climate, Sun</keywords_of_project>
		<duration_of_solution>long</duration_of_solution>
		<primary_SDG>Life on Land</primary_SDG>
		<secondary_SDG>             Climate Action,    </secondary_SDG>
		<country_of_contribution>Germany</country_of_contribution>
		<city_of_contribution>Aachen</city_of_contribution>
		<lat>50.778216</lat>
		<long>6.07825</long>
		<climate_hazard>meteorological biological</climate_hazard>
		<project_ID>230585066</project_ID>
		<no_of_images>3</no_of_images>
		<category_of_contribution>narrative_of_climate_change___</category_of_contribution>
		<extra_links>https://www.youtu.be/DAPffZiRkOw </extra_links>
	</project>
	<project ID="230866616">
		<Name>Raquel</Name>
		<Surname>Domingues</Surname>
		<Affiliation>Chalmers</Affiliation>
		<City_of_Institution>Gothenburg</City_of_Institution>
		<country_001>Sweden</country_001>
		<title_of_project>Acrodystopia</title_of_project>
		<credits_for_project>Ellen Boman, Chalmers University of Technology
Li Wallin, Chalmers University of Technology
Nelson Mouketa, Chalmers University of Technology
Raquel Domingues, Chalmers University of Technology</credits_for_project>
		<year_of_project>2021</year_of_project>
		<description_of_project>In this futuristic dystopian scenario where cities are flooded and civilisation as we know it has changed forever, people turn to innovation to survive.

Isolated on one of the citys last standing bridges, a group of people have developed the abandoned space into a secure settlement. Many years have passed since the uprising and a new society has risen from the rubble. The sea level is still high and most of the city is inaccessible without water travel. The ebb and flow have also reached new extremes, and the bridge floods when the tide is high.

The spherical pods are designed to roll and move on land, float and move on water, and connect with other pods to form a whole intricate system. The idea behind the adaptable approach is to make pods resilient to future emergencies. With them being so mobile, people are not as exposed to the new challenges they might face. Inspired by biomimicry, the outer shell rotates and steers the pod and can open up and let in light. Between the outer and inner shells is a layer of ball-bearing and hot air from the stove. Hot air insulation keeps the surrounding water from freezing.</description_of_project>
		<synopsis_of_project>We can create a new way of living by building a community-based society with adaptable housing and transportation pods, coping with water floods and scarcity, utilizing local resources, and incorporating innovations.</synopsis_of_project>
		<keywords_of_project>Adaptability, Resilience, Circularity, Community, Eco-Machines</keywords_of_project>
		<duration_of_solution>long</duration_of_solution>
		<primary_SDG>Sustainable Cities and Communities</primary_SDG>
		<secondary_SDG>             Climate Action,    </secondary_SDG>
		<country_of_contribution>Sweden</country_of_contribution>
		<city_of_contribution>Gothenburg</city_of_contribution>
		<lat>57.703991</lat>
		<long>11.962271</long>
		<climate_hazard>Hydrological</climate_hazard>
		<project_ID>230866616</project_ID>
		<no_of_images>3</no_of_images>
		<category_of_contribution>narrative_of_climate_change___</category_of_contribution>
		<extra_links>NA</extra_links>
	</project>
	<project ID="231111769">
		<Name>Mohamed</Name>
		<Surname>Yousry</Surname>
		<Affiliation>alexandria_university__egypt</Affiliation>
		<City_of_Institution>Alexandria</City_of_Institution>
		<country_001>Egypt</country_001>
		<title_of_project>Climate Change, Co2 impact and biomaterials, towards Net-Zero emissions.</title_of_project>
		<credits_for_project>Mohmad Assem Hanafy, Mai Mohamed Abdo, Mohamed Yousry Abo-El-Shohood, Marwan Sabry El Ashmawy, Dina Ibrahim Ramadan, Israa Yasser Nasrallah, Arwa AbdelHamid Foda, Yousef Mahmoud Saber, Fatma Mohamed Sleem, Alaa Salah El-Din El-Sawasany, Hend Mohamed Ashraf, Alaa kher manda</credits_for_project>
		<year_of_project>2023</year_of_project>
		<description_of_project>Our civilization is severely affected by climate change, which is shown in different phenomena, especially the CO2 emissions that are affecting the globe and resulting from human activities. As the manufacturing of construction materials in the building industry is considered one of the most significant causes of carbon emissions, the project investigates the potentials of different biomaterial solutions available in Egypt to replace the ordinary materials and develops their manufacturing processes in order to target the projects problem.</description_of_project>
		<synopsis_of_project>Re-designing the materials production process will reshape the future of our planet.</synopsis_of_project>
		<keywords_of_project>CO2,Air Pollution, Biomaterials, Chitin, Hydrogel skeleton</keywords_of_project>
		<duration_of_solution>long</duration_of_solution>
		<primary_SDG>Responsible Consumption and Production</primary_SDG>
		<secondary_SDG>         Industry, Innovation and Infrastructure,  Sustainable Cities and Communities, Responsible Consumption and Production,     </secondary_SDG>
		<country_of_contribution>Egypt</country_of_contribution>
		<city_of_contribution>Alexandria</city_of_contribution>
		<lat>31.2001</lat>
		<long>29.9187</long>
		<climate_hazard>climatological</climate_hazard>
		<project_ID>231111769</project_ID>
		<no_of_images>3</no_of_images>
		<category_of_contribution>solutions_to_adapt_to_climate_</category_of_contribution>
		<extra_links>NA</extra_links>
	</project>
	<project ID="231834314">
		<Name>Wian</Name>
		<Surname>Jordaan</Surname>
		<Affiliation>other</Affiliation>
		<City_of_Institution>Pretoria, City of Tshwane</City_of_Institution>
		<country_001>South_Africa</country_001>
		<title_of_project>From the ground up</title_of_project>
		<credits_for_project>Wian Jordaan, AuthorDesigner</credits_for_project>
		<year_of_project>2020</year_of_project>
		<description_of_project>The project is located in Melusi, an informal neighbourhood located in Pretoria, South Africa. The community of Melusi is largely dependent on external networks, resources and investment to support the communitys livelihood. Even though Melusis residents are highly resourceful, the lack of internal resources and support systems limit the communitys adaptive capacity and increase their vulnerability to the hazardous effects of climate change. 

The aim of the project is to provide a bottom-up approach, which enhances existing social, economic and environmental support systems within Melusi, to increase the adaptive capacity and climate change resilience of local residents. The project proposes to create a node of activity and communal facilities to complement the COPCs health clinic and community garden. The intervention will facilitate a process where local residents have the necessary resources, facilities and social support systems to improve their own quality of life and ability to adapt to future change.</description_of_project>
		<synopsis_of_project>Our attempt to address climate change should not be at the expense of the poor and vulnerable.</synopsis_of_project>
		<keywords_of_project>Facilitation, adaptation, process, vulnerability, informal</keywords_of_project>
		<duration_of_solution>permanent</duration_of_solution>
		<primary_SDG>Climate Action</primary_SDG>
		<secondary_SDG>   Good Health and Well-being,    Clean Water and Sanitation,     Sustainable Cities and Communities,      </secondary_SDG>
		<country_of_contribution>South_Africa</country_of_contribution>
		<city_of_contribution>Pretoria</city_of_contribution>
		<lat>-25.723736</lat>
		<long>28.12285</long>
		<climate_hazard>climatological</climate_hazard>
		<project_ID>231834314</project_ID>
		<no_of_images>3</no_of_images>
		<category_of_contribution>solutions_to_adapt_to_climate_</category_of_contribution>
		<extra_links>NA</extra_links>
	</project>
	<project ID="231911105">
		<Name>Pierre</Name>
		<Surname>Hugo</Surname>
		<Affiliation>university_of_pretoria</Affiliation>
		<City_of_Institution>Tshwane</City_of_Institution>
		<country_001>South_Africa</country_001>
		<title_of_project>Agrarian Haven</title_of_project>
		<credits_for_project>Pierre Hugo, Author</credits_for_project>
		<year_of_project>2022</year_of_project>
		<description_of_project>Ensuring sustainable food security is critical, especially in rapidly urbanising South African cities facing the consequences of climate change. This project aims to address this challenge by building a network that connects a food production facility that focuses on novel food production methods with urban farmers and the thriving informal market. This circular process of production, consumption, and waste ultimately minimises wasted energy and resources. Through adaptively reusing an existing building and opening the structure to public use, it allows communities to connect through shared experiences and spaces. This adaptability is further demonstrated by employing construction methods and materials designed for quick assembly and dismantling, including mass timber, repurposed bricks, and affordable local materials. Ultimately, the agrarian haven integrates food, economy, community, and education to create an empowering platform that will address the need for food security in South African urban cities.</description_of_project>
		<synopsis_of_project>The key to fighting hunger is food sovereignty.</synopsis_of_project>
		<keywords_of_project>Food Security, Urban Farming, Circular Economy, Waste Reduction, Community</keywords_of_project>
		<duration_of_solution>long</duration_of_solution>
		<primary_SDG>Zero Hunger</primary_SDG>
		<secondary_SDG>   Good Health and Well-being,              </secondary_SDG>
		<country_of_contribution>South_Africa</country_of_contribution>
		<city_of_contribution>Pretoria</city_of_contribution>
		<lat>-25.753202</lat>
		<long>28.206578</long>
		<climate_hazard>climatological</climate_hazard>
		<project_ID>231911105</project_ID>
		<no_of_images>3</no_of_images>
		<category_of_contribution>solutions_to_adapt_to_climate_</category_of_contribution>
		<extra_links>NA</extra_links>
	</project>
	<project ID="231983726">
		<Name>Julia</Name>
		<Surname>Pereira</Surname>
		<Affiliation>other</Affiliation>
		<City_of_Institution>Sao Carlos - Sao Paulo</City_of_Institution>
		<country_001>Brazil</country_001>
		<title_of_project>A brief history of Napras work and the riverside community way of life</title_of_project>
		<credits_for_project>Julia Martins, NAPRAs president 
Joao Pedro Sisternes, NAPRAs Member
Berenice Simao, Teacher of Sao Carlos do Jamari (Riverside community) 
Marcio Santana de Lima, Resident of Sao Carlos do Jamari (Riverside community)
Ana Sarah Lofti, NAPRAs ex-member
Sandila Alves, Poet from Sao Carlos do Jamari (Riverside community)</credits_for_project>
		<year_of_project>2022</year_of_project>
		<description_of_project>The NAPRA (Nucleus of Support for the Riverside Population of the Amazon) is a private non-profit organization founded in 1993 with the mission of contributing to the conservation of the Amazon Forest and valuing the way of life and culture of the populations that inhabit it.
Our goal is to develop projects together with communities and promote engagement between volunteers and riverside communities, strengthen social participation, visibility of the territory and also contribute to the learning process of students and professionals working in the Amazonian context.
We brought some short testimonies about the work of the institution and the riverside way of life, trying to resume the experience that we share with the communities, to show to all the world the difference in their way of life, consumption and what is it like to be in their territory. We sustain that sometimes the solution for climate change is to look into the traditional peoples who live together with nature.</description_of_project>
		<synopsis_of_project>The solution is hidden in the woods, with the people who live in harmony with the environment.</synopsis_of_project>
		<keywords_of_project>Riverside, ambiental education, ways of living, traditional people, Amazon.</keywords_of_project>
		<duration_of_solution>long</duration_of_solution>
		<primary_SDG>Sustainable Cities and Communities</primary_SDG>
		<secondary_SDG>            Responsible Consumption and Production, Climate Action,    Partnerships to achieve the Goal,</secondary_SDG>
		<country_of_contribution>Brazil</country_of_contribution>
		<city_of_contribution>Porto Velho</city_of_contribution>
		<lat>-8.427546</lat>
		<long>-63.533928</long>
		<climate_hazard>climatological Hydrological</climate_hazard>
		<project_ID>231983726</project_ID>
		<no_of_images>3</no_of_images>
		<category_of_contribution>narrative_of_climate_change___</category_of_contribution>
		<extra_links>https://www.napra.org.br/projetos/comunidades/</extra_links>
	</project>
	<project ID="231995872">
		<Name>Lisa</Name>
		<Surname>Safdal</Surname>
		<Affiliation>Chalmers</Affiliation>
		<City_of_Institution>Gothenburg</City_of_Institution>
		<country_001>Sweden</country_001>
		<title_of_project>[ POWER SWITCH ]</title_of_project>
		<credits_for_project>Delaney Davis, Author.
Amalia Athanasia Dimou, Author.
Lisa Safdal, Author.
Axel Uhren, Author.</credits_for_project>
		<year_of_project>2023</year_of_project>
		<description_of_project>In four days, Earth will be hit by a massive geomagnetic storm that will disturb the magnetosphere, knock out the power grid and fry our entire electronic infrastructure. The sun will push out waves of light, exposing the Earths surface to intense radiation. In search for protection from the hazardous rays, humans will be forced to settle underground. The polarity of society changes. New communities are built underground, and the old cities descend into chaos.

The years following the crisis, The prolonged exposure to radiation has caused some... strange... mutations to occur within the plants and animals Upstairs. The humans have learned how to adapt to life Downstairs.</description_of_project>
		<synopsis_of_project>Despite globalization, humanity is unequipped to collaborate to address an issue as impactful as an extreme solar storm-how can we better equip ourselves?</synopsis_of_project>
		<keywords_of_project>Geomagnetic storm, Blackout, Radiation, Life below ground, Social reformation</keywords_of_project>
		<duration_of_solution>long</duration_of_solution>
		<primary_SDG>Life on Land</primary_SDG>
		<secondary_SDG>           Sustainable Cities and Communities, Responsible Consumption and Production,     </secondary_SDG>
		<country_of_contribution>Sweden</country_of_contribution>
		<city_of_contribution>Gothenburg</city_of_contribution>
		<lat>57.74381</lat>
		<long>12.158866</long>
		<climate_hazard>meteorological</climate_hazard>
		<project_ID>231995872</project_ID>
		<no_of_images>2</no_of_images>
		<category_of_contribution>narrative_of_climate_change___</category_of_contribution>
		<extra_links>NA</extra_links>
	</project>
	<project ID="232020558">
		<Name>Elena</Name>
		<Surname>Cucchi</Surname>
		<Affiliation>Chalmers</Affiliation>
		<City_of_Institution>Gothenburg</City_of_Institution>
		<country_001>Sweden</country_001>
		<title_of_project>The emergency is now! - Live and play with water</title_of_project>
		<credits_for_project>Elena Cucchi, author
Ebba Gordon Hultsjo, author
Jessica Borjesson, author
Sadia Sharmin, author</credits_for_project>
		<year_of_project>2023</year_of_project>
		<description_of_project>Once upon a place and time, a city was born, Dhaka. Emerging from the fluid fabric of its surroundings, an irascible landscape. Dhaka looked full of life, and in symbiosis with all ecosystems - rivers, floodplains and agricultural fields. Growing up, her relationship with people started to change, but only a few of them recognized her tender landmass. They took away her green spaces, animals, and covered her in concrete and asphalt. Traffic and continuous construction made it impossible for her to breathe. Furious transformations, whether official, private, or spontaneous, succumbed to the regime of a dry ideology. 

Dhaka used to be in love with Ganga, the water, enjoying her playfulness with respect and care. Man did not understand the harmony between the two females and with brutal force he started pushing Ganga away from Dhaka, confining her into strong boundaries. She kept coming back to Dhaka every year with prosperous monsoons, but with the drastic increase of density and sea level rise, the water transformed into aggressive floods spreading fear and diseases. What if Ganga decides to reunite with her beloved Dhaka? What if Ganga returns with a message of hope, teaching children to live in harmony with nature?</description_of_project>
		<synopsis_of_project>We must learn to live with nature to build a resilient future!</synopsis_of_project>
		<keywords_of_project>resilience, storytelling, feminist approach, flooding, climate change</keywords_of_project>
		<duration_of_solution>long</duration_of_solution>
		<primary_SDG>Sustainable Cities and Communities</primary_SDG>
		<secondary_SDG>   Good Health and Well-being,  Gender Equality,        Climate Action,    </secondary_SDG>
		<country_of_contribution>Bangladesh</country_of_contribution>
		<city_of_contribution>Dhaka</city_of_contribution>
		<lat>23.753925</lat>
		<long>90.395898</long>
		<climate_hazard>Hydrological</climate_hazard>
		<project_ID>232020558</project_ID>
		<no_of_images>3</no_of_images>
		<category_of_contribution>narrative_of_climate_change___</category_of_contribution>
		<extra_links>NA</extra_links>
	</project>
	<project ID="232144352">
		<Name>Lue-Shane</Name>
		<Surname>Cloete</Surname>
		<Affiliation>other</Affiliation>
		<City_of_Institution>Pretoria</City_of_Institution>
		<country_001>South_Africa</country_001>
		<title_of_project>Why do we waste so much?</title_of_project>
		<credits_for_project>Lue-Shane Cloete, Author</credits_for_project>
		<year_of_project>2021</year_of_project>
		<description_of_project>This project aims to change the perceptions around waste. Only 6  of South Africans recycle their household waste and this can be attributed to the lack of resources, infrastructure and education that supports ethical waste management practices.  Through an analysis of household waste in a Highrise residential building in Sunnyside, Pretoria, South Africa, this project proposes multiple integrated spatial and infrastructural systems that aims to minimize the amount of waste sent to landfill. 

Organic waste is broken down in a Bioreactor and transformed into fuel and a nutrient. These products are utilized in the production of hot water and a new clip-on food production facade. Inorganic waste management is underpinned by circular economic principles where products like cardboard, glass and aluminum are sold to recycling depos in the city via waste pickers, which in turn, support their families on the proceeds. 

This project finds that waste is valuable and should be considered as a recourse that can be utilized to supplement the infrastructural needs of impoverished communities in South Africa whilst reducing the amount of  waste sent to landfill.</description_of_project>
		<synopsis_of_project>Waste is valuable, use it.</synopsis_of_project>
		<keywords_of_project>Bioreactor, Food Facade, Circular Economy,</keywords_of_project>
		<duration_of_solution>permanent</duration_of_solution>
		<primary_SDG>Sustainable Cities and Communities</primary_SDG>
		<secondary_SDG>  Zero Hunger,       Industry, Innovation and Infrastructure,   Responsible Consumption and Production,     </secondary_SDG>
		<country_of_contribution>South_Africa</country_of_contribution>
		<city_of_contribution>Pretoria</city_of_contribution>
		<lat>-25.745945</lat>
		<long>28.188302</long>
		<climate_hazard>meteorological</climate_hazard>
		<project_ID>232144352</project_ID>
		<no_of_images>3</no_of_images>
		<category_of_contribution>solutions_to_adapt_to_climate_</category_of_contribution>
		<extra_links>NA</extra_links>
	</project>
	<project ID="232203458">
		<Name>Hano</Name>
		<Surname>Venter</Surname>
		<Affiliation>other</Affiliation>
		<City_of_Institution>Cape Town</City_of_Institution>
		<country_001>South_Africa</country_001>
		<title_of_project>The Melusi Agricultural Community Centre</title_of_project>
		<credits_for_project>Hano Venter, Author</credits_for_project>
		<year_of_project>2020</year_of_project>
		<description_of_project>This intervention attempts to provide Melusi with climate resilient strategies with regards to agriculture and
nutrition. By utilising the existing agricultural and cultural knowledge of the residents of Melusi, the Centre would
attempt to breed new varieties of plants - specifically suited to the Melusi context and climate.
This adaptation would allow the plants to be bred in the present for the inevitable increase in temperature in
the future. Along with supplying Melusi with climatically and contextual appropriate plants and crops, the skills
of the community is to be developed and enhanced.
As a side benefit of the plant breeding programme, the produce grown at the Centre is to be distributed to the
clinic or the Melusi community for consumption or for spreading information on proper nutrition by the Primary Care unit stationed at Melusi.</description_of_project>
		<synopsis_of_project>The key to uncovering climatic resilience lies in the co-development of the community.</synopsis_of_project>
		<keywords_of_project>agro-ecology, communal knowledge sharing, urban agriculture, cultural knowledge, agricultural climate adaptation</keywords_of_project>
		<duration_of_solution>long</duration_of_solution>
		<primary_SDG>Zero Hunger</primary_SDG>
		<secondary_SDG>   Good Health and Well-being,           Life Below Water,   Partnerships to achieve the Goal,</secondary_SDG>
		<country_of_contribution>South_Africa</country_of_contribution>
		<city_of_contribution>Melusi, Pretoria, South Africa</city_of_contribution>
		<lat>-25.723771</lat>
		<long>28.120397</long>
		<climate_hazard>climatological Hydrological biological</climate_hazard>
		<project_ID>232203458</project_ID>
		<no_of_images>3</no_of_images>
		<category_of_contribution>narrative_of_climate_change___</category_of_contribution>
		<extra_links>NA</extra_links>
	</project>
	<project ID="232253503">
		<Name>Amany</Name>
		<Surname>Abdel-Aziz</Surname>
		<Affiliation>alexandria_university__egypt</Affiliation>
		<City_of_Institution>Alexandria</City_of_Institution>
		<country_001>Egypt</country_001>
		<title_of_project>Proposal for Climate-resilient City as solution for water level rise.</title_of_project>
		<credits_for_project>Amany Abdel-Aziz, faculty of engineering, Alexandria university, department of architecture.
Abdelhamid ahmed abdelhamid,faculty of engineering, Alexandria university, department of architecture.
Amr Elsayed Mohamed,faculty of engineering, Alexandria university, department of architecture
Maryam Fouad, faculty of engineering, Alexandria university, department of architecture
Hajar Mohamed Shebl, faculty of engineering, Alexandria university, department of architecture.
Abanoub saadalla , faculty of engineering, Alexandria university, department of architecture.
Abdelrahman khaled said ,faculty of engineering, Alexandria university, department of architecture.
Ashraf Samy Gaber,faculty of engineering, Alexandria university, department of architecture.
Yomna Samy Fathy ,faculty of engineering, Alexandria university, department of architecture.
Rahma Mohammed Sobhy ,faculty of engineering, Alexandria university, department of architecture.
Taiser Badr Mostafa ,faculty of engineering, Alexandria university, department of architecture.</credits_for_project>
		<year_of_project>2023</year_of_project>
		<description_of_project>As the effects of climate change become more apparent, it is essential that we take proactive steps to mitigate their impact. One of the most pressing issues facing cities today is the rise in sea levels caused by melting glaciers and polar ice caps. While traditional methods of resistance can be effective, they are not always sustainable or cost-effective. Instead, a more adaptable approach that focuses on nature-based solutions can generate new opportunities for sustainable growth, green spaces, and improved living conditions.
Our proposal for a climate resilient city centers around the idea of adaptability. Rather than fighting the rising tide, we will work with nature to find solutions that are sustainable and cost-effective. This approach includes creating green spaces, such as parks and community gardens, that can act as natural buffers against rising sea levels. These spaces will also provide opportunities for recreation, socialization, and improved mental health.</description_of_project>
		<synopsis_of_project>To adapt to natural crises through innovative ideas that allows us to thrive in their aftermath.</synopsis_of_project>
		<keywords_of_project>Climate-resilient city, water-level rise, sustainability, efficient community, green infrastructure</keywords_of_project>
		<duration_of_solution>long</duration_of_solution>
		<primary_SDG>Sustainable Cities and Communities</primary_SDG>
		<secondary_SDG>             Climate Action,    </secondary_SDG>
		<country_of_contribution>Egypt</country_of_contribution>
		<city_of_contribution>Alexandria</city_of_contribution>
		<lat>31.205753</lat>
		<long>29.924526</long>
		<climate_hazard>climatological</climate_hazard>
		<project_ID>232253503</project_ID>
		<no_of_images>3</no_of_images>
		<category_of_contribution>solutions_to_adapt_to_climate_</category_of_contribution>
		<extra_links>No</extra_links>
	</project>
	<project ID="232265347">
		<Name>Adrian</Name>
		<Surname>Buffa</Surname>
		<Affiliation>other</Affiliation>
		<City_of_Institution>Pretoria</City_of_Institution>
		<country_001>South_Africa</country_001>
		<title_of_project>Building community through collaboration</title_of_project>
		<credits_for_project>Adrian Buffa, University of Pretoria</credits_for_project>
		<year_of_project>2020</year_of_project>
		<description_of_project>This investigation takes place in Melusi, a rapidly developing informal settlement to the north west of Pretorias CBD. Its current level of infrastructural deficit and lack of accessible
healthcare facilities contribute to a high degree of vulnerability to internal and external shocks - leading to major health risks for residents. This necessitates an approach to future
development which facilitates the generation of appropriate community-driven responses to these issues. The intention of the proposed intervention is the provision of primary community healthcare infrastructure (including social and spiritual support spaces), which is flexible, and adaptable by community members, in order to respond to shocks such as the Covid-19 pandemic. A layered, incremental intervention is proposed to ensure adaptability and
equitable community-led growth alongside the provision of essential healthcare services.</description_of_project>
		<synopsis_of_project>Community-led collaborative development can help improve the health and well being of vulnerable communities.</synopsis_of_project>
		<keywords_of_project>Incremental, community-led, healthcare, informal settlement, infrastructure</keywords_of_project>
		<duration_of_solution>long</duration_of_solution>
		<primary_SDG>Good Health and Well-being</primary_SDG>
		<secondary_SDG>           Sustainable Cities and Communities,  Climate Action,    Partnerships to achieve the Goal,</secondary_SDG>
		<country_of_contribution>South_Africa</country_of_contribution>
		<city_of_contribution>Pretoria</city_of_contribution>
		<lat>-25.724158</lat>
		<long>28.122767</long>
		<climate_hazard>biological</climate_hazard>
		<project_ID>232265347</project_ID>
		<no_of_images>3</no_of_images>
		<category_of_contribution>narrative_of_climate_change___</category_of_contribution>
		<extra_links>NA</extra_links>
	</project>
	<project ID="232318113">
		<Name>Melicia</Name>
		<Surname>van Loggerenberg</Surname>
		<Affiliation>other</Affiliation>
		<City_of_Institution>Pretoria</City_of_Institution>
		<country_001>South_Africa</country_001>
		<title_of_project>Independence through Interface</title_of_project>
		<credits_for_project>Melicia van Loggerenberg</credits_for_project>
		<year_of_project>2021</year_of_project>
		<description_of_project>Finding out what really happens after a building is finished doesnt seem to be anyones job... (Feireiss and Bouman, 2011)

The covid pandemic has brought about a period of release where new ways of living has resulted in an economic crisis. If our aim is to move towards regenerative thinking, then we need to redesign the current system to one that projects a positive future narrative where buildings are able to react to changing conditions. In the development of this scheme, I attempted to follow a more deep-seated, personal approach to Green building. This building practice required an understanding of the social, physical and economic diversity of a place. It adopted a notion of imperfect knowledge that would enable architectural interventions to serve as an evolving prototype where built environment professionals can begin to better understand a buildings responsibility in relation to its urban surroundings over time.

These theories were put to the test in a readaptation scheme where an empty office building was transformed into a mixed-use residential building. The aim of the readapting focused on making the structure more responsive to the contextual climate. This was achieved by turning the two main occupiable zones of the building to face true North and in doing so allow the North Eastern wind to passively cool the structure. The addition of secondary hallways would improve the extent of passive ventilation.

Furthermore, green pockets and wet balconies were positioned on the main ventilation axes, cooling the air before it moves through the building.

And finally the tectonic frame that wraps the structure would respond visually to the changes in atmospheric temperatures. This would become a visual warning, to both the building residents as well as the whole of Sunny Side, that outside temperatures are becoming hazardous.</description_of_project>
		<synopsis_of_project>I am of the belief that a more deep-seated personal approach to Green building practices holds the key to involving smaller local actors in addressing bigger systemic issues.</synopsis_of_project>
		<keywords_of_project>Interface, Independence, Micro-climates, Adaptable, Ownership</keywords_of_project>
		<duration_of_solution>long</duration_of_solution>
		<primary_SDG>Sustainable Cities and Communities</primary_SDG>
		<secondary_SDG>             Climate Action,    </secondary_SDG>
		<country_of_contribution>South_Africa</country_of_contribution>
		<city_of_contribution>Pretoria</city_of_contribution>
		<lat>-25.751855</lat>
		<long>28.204962</long>
		<climate_hazard>meteorological</climate_hazard>
		<project_ID>232318113</project_ID>
		<no_of_images>3</no_of_images>
		<category_of_contribution>solutions_to_adapt_to_climate_</category_of_contribution>
		<extra_links>NA</extra_links>
	</project>
	<project ID="232322002">
		<Name>Nouran</Name>
		<Surname>Naguib</Surname>
		<Affiliation>alexandria_university__egypt</Affiliation>
		<City_of_Institution>Alexandria</City_of_Institution>
		<country_001>Egypt</country_001>
		<title_of_project>climate change sea level rise</title_of_project>
		<credits_for_project>Nouran Mohamed Naguib, Assistant Lecturer, supervisor
Ebtihal El-sayed Meliha, student
Menatallah Gaber Mostafa, student
Menna Ali Khamis, student
Abdelrahman El Sayed, student
Mennatallah Nabil Hussein, student
Abeer Atia Gaber, student
Mayar Ehab Saad, Student
Kareem Mohamed El-Sayed, student
Mohamed Gamal Abd El-Fatah, student
Abdel-rahman Zakaria, student</credits_for_project>
		<year_of_project>2023</year_of_project>
		<description_of_project>The climate change phenomenon  has a negative impact on various environments. The problems resulting from this phenomenon were presented, such as sea level rise, drought, loss of biodiversity, and high marine temperatures. The team delved into the problem of sea level rise associated with the seas and oceans, which plays a fundamental role In reducing global greenhouse gas emissions and stabilizing the Earths climate, as a result of the high temperatures associated with the phenomenon of climate change, melting of glaciers occurs and expansion of sea and ocean waters, so the level rises to affect negatively in the form of floods in other regions, which causes damage to those regions. After an interview with a group of specialized academics, the method of dealing with the problem and the available local solutions in the Delta of Egypt were discussed, specifically in the Kafr El-Sheikh governorate, whose population is seriously exposed to the threat of rising sea levels, like other governorates of the northern coast of Egypt, as a result of the rise in water levels, its creep from the shore and the penetration of its salinity. With soil spoil crops, damage homes, and disrupt interests. Therefore, the primitive methods used by the local population were put forward and were adopted and developed later, such as the use of double-layered wicker dams on the beaches to confine the sand between them, thus forming sustainable environmentally friendly dams, and then presenting the positive results of those dams in resolving the crisis. The project was well received by the state, to be partnered with the United Nations to develop it to extend 69 km along the northern coast, with the aim of saving 17 million people.
This example was shown to be a model among the many models in the world that provide effective solutions to save the planet.</description_of_project>
		<synopsis_of_project>We have one planet, lets swim towards saving it.</synopsis_of_project>
		<keywords_of_project>Climate Action, Sea level rise, Resilience, Gender Equality, Local Communities</keywords_of_project>
		<duration_of_solution>long</duration_of_solution>
		<primary_SDG>Sustainable Cities and Communities</primary_SDG>
		<secondary_SDG>     Gender Equality,   Decent Work and Economic Growth,     Climate Action,    </secondary_SDG>
		<country_of_contribution>Egypt</country_of_contribution>
		<city_of_contribution>Kafr el-sheikh</city_of_contribution>
		<lat>31.41515</lat>
		<long>30.876861</long>
		<climate_hazard>climatological</climate_hazard>
		<project_ID>232322002</project_ID>
		<no_of_images>3</no_of_images>
		<category_of_contribution>narrative_of_climate_change___</category_of_contribution>
		<extra_links>NA</extra_links>
	</project>
	<project ID="232327065">
		<Name>Jala</Name>
		<Surname>Hemdan</Surname>
		<Affiliation>alexandria_university__egypt</Affiliation>
		<City_of_Institution>Alexandria</City_of_Institution>
		<country_001>Egypt</country_001>
		<title_of_project>Urban Heat Island Effect</title_of_project>
		<credits_for_project>Belal Ahmed , Alexandria University
Omnia Zaghloul , Alexandria University
Sama Ahmed, Alexandria University
Ashrakat Walid, Alexandria University
Hannah Mansour , Alexandria University
Sara Samir, Alexandria University
Hania Osama , Alexandria University
Aya Ossama , Alexandria University
Mohamed El-Mallah, Alexandria University
Sohaila Salah, Alexandria University</credits_for_project>
		<year_of_project>2022</year_of_project>
		<description_of_project>An urban heat island is an urban area that is significantly warmer than its surrounding rural areas due to human activities. The temperature difference Is usually larger at night than during the day, and is most apparent when Winds are weak. UHI is most noticeable during the summer. It occurs when cities replace natural land cover with structures such as buildings, roads, and other infrastructure that absorb and re-emit the suns heat more than natural landscapes such as Forests and water Bodies. The urban heat island effect represents an important environmental problem facing all large urban centers. As a result this serious issue must be taken into consideration through various solutions according to the latest movements towards saving the planet from climate change.</description_of_project>
		<synopsis_of_project>The urban heat island effect represents an important environmental problem facing all large urban centers.</synopsis_of_project>
		<keywords_of_project>urban heat island, climate, sustainability, treatment, flood</keywords_of_project>
		<duration_of_solution>long</duration_of_solution>
		<primary_SDG>Sustainable Cities and Communities</primary_SDG>
		<secondary_SDG>             Climate Action,  Life on Land,  </secondary_SDG>
		<country_of_contribution>Egypt</country_of_contribution>
		<city_of_contribution>Alexandria</city_of_contribution>
		<lat>31.211921</lat>
		<long>30.167536</long>
		<climate_hazard>Hydrological</climate_hazard>
		<project_ID>232327065</project_ID>
		<no_of_images>2</no_of_images>
		<category_of_contribution>solutions_to_adapt_to_climate_</category_of_contribution>
		<extra_links>No</extra_links>
	</project>
	<project ID="232340040">
		<Name>Laura</Name>
		<Surname>Estrada</Surname>
		<Affiliation>Chalmers</Affiliation>
		<City_of_Institution>Gothenburg</City_of_Institution>
		<country_001>Sweden</country_001>
		<title_of_project>Speculative flooding scenario in Santa Monica Pier</title_of_project>
		<credits_for_project>Adam Back Thoren, author
Gwendolyn Bauer, author
Laura Estrada, author
Ida Ylenfors, author</credits_for_project>
		<year_of_project>2022</year_of_project>
		<description_of_project>The poster presents a possible future scenario where Santa Monica, California is flooded due to the sea level rising and the overexploitation of sand as a construction resource. In this scenario, Three different approaches compete to tackle the challenge through either technology, environmental innovation or social resilience; these approximations see the key to a resilience design according to their particular interests and lack an holistic perspective of the situation, so the municipality decides to combine the three proposals. Nonetheless, the threat of an innominate catastrophic earthquake makes us question in this installation if it is truly sustainable to put all these efforts and resources to maintain resilience in such a vulnerable location.</description_of_project>
		<synopsis_of_project>Resilience design needs to be an adaptive, there is no final concept, no final solution, we need each other to evolve our plans and thrive together.</synopsis_of_project>
		<keywords_of_project>resilience, flooding, sustainability, cooperation, design</keywords_of_project>
		<duration_of_solution>short</duration_of_solution>
		<primary_SDG>Sustainable Cities and Communities</primary_SDG>
		<secondary_SDG>             Climate Action,  Life on Land,  </secondary_SDG>
		<country_of_contribution>United_States</country_of_contribution>
		<city_of_contribution>Santa Monica</city_of_contribution>
		<lat>34.006856</lat>
		<long>-118.496966</long>
		<climate_hazard>Hydrological</climate_hazard>
		<project_ID>232340040</project_ID>
		<no_of_images>3</no_of_images>
		<category_of_contribution>narrative_of_climate_change___</category_of_contribution>
		<extra_links>NA</extra_links>
	</project>
	<project ID="232376874">
		<Name>Adrienne</Name>
		<Surname>MacDonald</Surname>
		<Affiliation>university_of_pretoria</Affiliation>
		<City_of_Institution>Pretoria</City_of_Institution>
		<country_001>South_Africa</country_001>
		<title_of_project>Public Node Development Through Water Infrastructure</title_of_project>
		<credits_for_project>Mitchell Austin
Susanna Swanepoel
Adrienne MacDonald</credits_for_project>
		<year_of_project>2022</year_of_project>
		<description_of_project>The aim of this project was to understand the vulnerability of
the local community and develop an adaptation
response strategy using the public realm as a structuring
device.
This project explores the complex roles of spatial nodes
and water supply in Melusi (an informal settlement in
Tshwane, South Africa), through an examination of its contextual
setting and spatial characteristics.
Through a series of mapping exercises, and an
understanding of risk in conjunction with "informality"
and "public space," the possible vulnerabilities and
opportunities within Melusi are unpacked.
From this, arises the potential of an intimate relationship
between spatial nodes, and water supply infrastructure.
The project reflect on the possible socio-economic effects of
such an intervention, all the while learning from the
locals "Melusian" way of life.</description_of_project>
		<synopsis_of_project>Resilient informal settlements can utilise small infrastructural inputs to mitigate climate change</synopsis_of_project>
		<keywords_of_project>Climate change, Resilience, Nodes, Water infrastructure, Vulnerability</keywords_of_project>
		<duration_of_solution>short</duration_of_solution>
		<primary_SDG> Clean Water and Sanitation</primary_SDG>
		<secondary_SDG>           Sustainable Cities and Communities,      </secondary_SDG>
		<country_of_contribution>South_Africa</country_of_contribution>
		<city_of_contribution>Tswhane</city_of_contribution>
		<lat>-25.723132</lat>
		<long>28.11676</long>
		<climate_hazard>climatological</climate_hazard>
		<project_ID>232376874</project_ID>
		<no_of_images>3</no_of_images>
		<category_of_contribution>solutions_to_adapt_to_climate_</category_of_contribution>
		<extra_links>NA</extra_links>
	</project>
	<project ID="232421110">
		<Name>Veronica</Name>
		<Surname>Garcia Donoso</Surname>
		<Affiliation>other</Affiliation>
		<City_of_Institution>I am a Professor at the Federal University of Santa Maria, Cachoeira do Sul-RS (Brazil). Currently experienced researcher living in Monchengladbach, Germany.</City_of_Institution>
		<country_001>Brazil</country_001>
		<title_of_project>Rainforest importance for climate change and the relevance of ecological planning for cities within forest areas</title_of_project>
		<credits_for_project>Prof. Dr. Veronica Garcia Donoso, Professor at the Federal University of Santa Maria (UFSM), Brazil; Experienced Researcher, Alexander von Humboldt Foundation, Germany.</credits_for_project>
		<year_of_project>2023</year_of_project>
		<description_of_project>The Amazon region is globally crucial for the biodiversity and climate system. Many studies have suggested that the global warming and deforestation combined can push the Amazon rainforest beyond critical limits. New technologies and satellite images have made it possible to monitor forest cover. However, the sequence of actions needs political, economic and cultural global support.
From 1985 to 2021, the forest area in the Brazilian Amazon reduced 44,1 Mha; the loss of forest is related with the increase of pasture areas for livestock, with increased from around 37 Mha in the same period.
 Brazils southern state, Rondoni, is subject to deforestation through clearing land for livestock, agriculture and urban areas. This situation results in rain falls in longer massive bursts and flooding reaching records. Education of the communities within and beyond the Amazon is essential in maintaining the regions biodiversity and raising awareness on climate mitigation.</description_of_project>
		<synopsis_of_project>Rainforest importance for climate change and the relevance of ecological planning for cities within forest areas</synopsis_of_project>
		<keywords_of_project>Amazon, Rondonia, Deforestation, Climate Change, Cities.</keywords_of_project>
		<duration_of_solution>long</duration_of_solution>
		<primary_SDG>Sustainable Cities and Communities</primary_SDG>
		<secondary_SDG>             Climate Action,    </secondary_SDG>
		<country_of_contribution>Brazil</country_of_contribution>
		<city_of_contribution>Porto Velho-RO</city_of_contribution>
		<lat>-8.752724</lat>
		<long>-63.887159</long>
		<climate_hazard>climatological Hydrological</climate_hazard>
		<project_ID>232421110</project_ID>
		<no_of_images>1</no_of_images>
		<category_of_contribution>narrative_of_climate_change___</category_of_contribution>
		<extra_links>No.</extra_links>
	</project>
	<project ID="232442630">
		<Name>Pia Alejandra</Name>
		<Surname>Galvez Lindegaard</Surname>
		<Affiliation>other</Affiliation>
		<City_of_Institution>Complutense University of Madrid</City_of_Institution>
		<country_001>Spain</country_001>
		<title_of_project>Annotations</title_of_project>
		<credits_for_project>Pia Galvez, Faculty of Fine Arts Complutense University of Madrid</credits_for_project>
		<year_of_project>2023</year_of_project>
		<description_of_project>I am narrating what I normally observe. I am reporting some events which got my attention and are associated to different biological or hydrological hazards.
Even if they could be related or not to my daily life, they are relevant for my ongoing artistic research.</description_of_project>
		<synopsis_of_project>Focus on what yo can do: positive impacts and behavioral changes.</synopsis_of_project>
		<keywords_of_project>artistic research, research-creation, environmental arts, ocean, water</keywords_of_project>
		<duration_of_solution>short long permanent</duration_of_solution>
		<primary_SDG>Climate Action</primary_SDG>
		<secondary_SDG>           Sustainable Cities and Communities,   Life Below Water, Life on Land,  </secondary_SDG>
		<country_of_contribution>Spain</country_of_contribution>
		<city_of_contribution>Madrid</city_of_contribution>
		<lat>40.440264</lat>
		<long>-3.733861</long>
		<climate_hazard>Hydrological biological</climate_hazard>
		<project_ID>232442630</project_ID>
		<no_of_images>3</no_of_images>
		<category_of_contribution>narrative_of_climate_change___</category_of_contribution>
		<extra_links>NA</extra_links>
	</project>
	<project ID="232473032">
		<Name>Tessa</Name>
		<Surname>van Mourik</Surname>
		<Affiliation>tu_delft__the_netherlands</Affiliation>
		<City_of_Institution>Delft</City_of_Institution>
		<country_001>Netherlands</country_001>
		<title_of_project>Symbiotic Urban Movement</title_of_project>
		<credits_for_project>Annemiek Braunius, Transition Expert SUM 
Nando Versteeg, Transition Expert SUM
Nikki de Zeeuw, Transition Expert SUM
Andy van den Dobbelsteen, Sustainability Project Coordinator</credits_for_project>
		<year_of_project>2022</year_of_project>
		<description_of_project>Symbiotic Urban Movement (SUM) was the Solar Decathlon team of TU Delft. The students developed net- positive energy strategies targeting 847.000 underperforming rental flats in the Netherlands. SUMs ambition was to achieve a mutually beneficial relationship between the user, the community, and the environment.

The top-up apartments are prefabricated, modular and biobased. They can be lifted onto the existing building and become the powerplant of the entire block, covered with solar panels on roof and facade. They can also collect rainwater for toilet flushing and plants. In reverse, the existing building provides the foundation for the new apartments. Symbiosis!</description_of_project>
		<synopsis_of_project>With our tenement flat repurposing strategy we would like to make a world where diversity, innovation and social interaction are stimulated. Where clever design solutions can tackle social, economic and environmental challenges.</synopsis_of_project>
		<keywords_of_project>Teamwork, innovation, multidiscplinary, sustainable design, future</keywords_of_project>
		<duration_of_solution>long</duration_of_solution>
		<primary_SDG>Sustainable Cities and Communities</primary_SDG>
		<secondary_SDG>             Climate Action,    </secondary_SDG>
		<country_of_contribution>Netherlands</country_of_contribution>
		<city_of_contribution>Delft</city_of_contribution>
		<lat>52.005786</lat>
		<long>4.370418</long>
		<climate_hazard>meteorological climatological</climate_hazard>
		<project_ID>232473032</project_ID>
		<no_of_images>3</no_of_images>
		<category_of_contribution>solutions_to_adapt_to_climate_</category_of_contribution>
		<extra_links>https://www.delftsolardecathlon.com/</extra_links>
	</project>
	<project ID="232481759">
		<Name>Yasmin</Name>
		<Surname>Anefalos de Oliveira</Surname>
		<Affiliation>other</Affiliation>
		<City_of_Institution>Sao Paulo</City_of_Institution>
		<country_001>Brazil</country_001>
		<title_of_project>Territory of Interest of Culture and Landscape Jaragua-Perus-Anhanguera - Sao Paulo, Brazil</title_of_project>
		<credits_for_project>Euler Sandeville Jr., Center for Landscape Studies, Senior Professor at the University of Sao Paulo
Yasmin Anefalos de Oliveira, Center for Landscape Studies, University of Sao Paulo
Valdirene Ijano, Center for Landscape Studies, University of Sao Paulo
Natalia Teixeira Lopes da Costa, Center for Landscape Studies, University of Sao Paulo
Patricia Siqueira Melo Center for Landscape Studies, University of Sao Paulo and Integrated Center for Youth and Adult Education Perus I
Gabriela Yi Zhu Chan, Center for Landscape Studies, University of Sao Paulo
Regina Celia Soares Bortoto, Coruja Colective, Paulista Heritage Education Network
Marcio Antonio Melhado Bezerra, Coruja Colective, Paulo Freire Colective
Mario Sergio Bortoto, Coruja Colective, Paulista Heritage Education Network
Maria Helena Bertolini Bezerra, Projeto Coruja, Paulo Freire Collective
Pedro Augusto Bertolini Bezerra, University of Sao Paulo, EMEF CEU - Municipal Elementary School of the Unified Educational Center Perus
Gisele Costa, member of Parque Anhanguera Management Council Management 20222024, Schedules
Juliana Costa (narration)
Cleiton Ferreira, Quilombaque Cultural Community, Agendas
Jose Queiroz, Quilombaque Cultural Community (Soro, in memorian)
Sirlei Bertolini, member of Representative on the Council for the Environment and Sustainability Subprefecture Pirituba Jaragua
Suerda Deboa, Morada Jaragua Collective and Cultural Space, member of Representative on the Council for the Environment and Sustainability Subprefecture Pirituba Jaragua


All authors integrate the movement for the Territory of Interest of Culture and Landscape Jaragua-Perus-Anhanguera and the Free and Collaborative University project.</credits_for_project>
		<year_of_project>2023</year_of_project>
		<description_of_project>We are a Brazilian collective working in the territory Jaragua-Perus-Anhanguera, three outskirt districts in the northwest region of Sao Paulo city, which integrate the biosphere reserve of the municipality. Since 2011, the movement for the Reappropriation of the Perus Cement Factory, the Quilombaque Cultural Community, the Coruja collective, in continuity to the Queixada labor movement, with the Center for Landscape Studies at FAU-USP, have been developing with other social actors the Free and Collaborative University project, integrating local and academic knowledge under the principles of nonviolent resistance and permanent endurance. We created in the citys 2014 Master Plan an innovative urbanistic instrument called the "Territory of Interest of Culture and Landscape Jaragua-Perus-Anhanguera", which integrates education, culture and environment and it is based on social participation and the building of knowledge for a more supportive and sustainable city. We work with educational, cultural and popular museology projects, seeking to generate local income and socio-environmental solutions responsive to the climate and the urban changes in the preservation of the natural and the cultural heritage and the landscape richness as a collective patrimony. There is a lot to do and we are doing it. Join us!</description_of_project>
		<synopsis_of_project>To hope for the future acting collaboratively in the present for a fairer and more sustainable environment.</synopsis_of_project>
		<keywords_of_project>Environment, Education, Culture, Landscape, Social Participation</keywords_of_project>
		<duration_of_solution>long</duration_of_solution>
		<primary_SDG>Sustainable Cities and Communities</primary_SDG>
		<secondary_SDG>    Quality Education,    Decent Work and Economic Growth,  Reduced Inequality,       </secondary_SDG>
		<country_of_contribution>Brazil</country_of_contribution>
		<city_of_contribution>Sao Paulo</city_of_contribution>
		<lat>-23.41812</lat>
		<long>-46.766466</long>
		<climate_hazard>Hydrological</climate_hazard>
		<project_ID>232481759</project_ID>
		<no_of_images>3</no_of_images>
		<category_of_contribution>solutions_to_adapt_to_climate_</category_of_contribution>
		<extra_links>NA</extra_links>
	</project>
	<project ID="232487583">
		<Name>Kevin</Name>
		<Surname>Moreno Gata</Surname>
		<Affiliation>rwth_aachen__germany</Affiliation>
		<City_of_Institution>Aachen</City_of_Institution>
		<country_001>Germany</country_001>
		<title_of_project>Construction methods with naturally grown timber</title_of_project>
		<credits_for_project>- (Kevin Moreno Gata, Denis Grizmann, Martin Trautz) Chair of Structures and Structural Design - RWTH Aachen
- (Florian Spahn, Sven Klinkel) Chair of Structural Analysis and Dynamics - RWTH Aachen
- (Robert Koller, Ulrich Schurr) Institute of Plant Sciences (IBG-2) - Forschungszentrum Julich
- (Andreas Wintraken) Wald und Holz NRW
- ( Elif Akbas,  Yara Almojaber,  Adonis Alsaad,  Yo Han Choi,  Tobias Gruters,  Baiyi Guo,  Ana Hernando de la Fuente,  Lana Karamani,  Cristian Moscoso Lizama,  Irma Softic,  Sheldon Stephens, Raman Suliman,  Viktor Wages) Architecture students - RWTH Aachen.</credits_for_project>
		<year_of_project>2023</year_of_project>
		<description_of_project>The timber construction industry has the potential to be a sustainable solution, but it heavily relies on standard cross-sections and semi-finished parts, resulting in a significant amount of waste. Modern forestry operations are designed to produce straight, knot-free timber, resulting in the abandonment of irregularities such as curved elements or forks, which are not suitable for construction.
However, building requirements vary significantly, and each site has unique needs. This research project questions the current approach to timber extraction and use and integrates residual elements found in the forest. By analyzing the mechanical properties of these elements, the project aims to show that they can be integrated into building structures. This approach could pave the way for a more sustainable and adaptable timber construction industry capable of meeting each building sites unique requirements and reducing material needs.
The project is carried out by an interdisciplinary team of architects, civil engineers, biologists, and architecture students in collaboration with the Aachen forestry team. The objective is to design a demonstration structure for a pedestrian bridge that will be integrated into the forest surroundings using materials collected from the forest.</description_of_project>
		<synopsis_of_project>An interdisciplinary research project aims to integrate residual forest elements and analyze their mechanical properties for potential integration into building structures, paving the way for a more sustainable and adaptable timber construction industry.</synopsis_of_project>
		<keywords_of_project>Tree growth, Forest, Timber construction, Mechanical properties, Interdisciplinary team</keywords_of_project>
		<duration_of_solution>long permanent</duration_of_solution>
		<primary_SDG>Responsible Consumption and Production</primary_SDG>
		<secondary_SDG>       Affordable and Clean Energy,  Industry, Innovation and Infrastructure,    Climate Action,    </secondary_SDG>
		<country_of_contribution>Germany</country_of_contribution>
		<city_of_contribution>Aachen</city_of_contribution>
		<lat>50.683633</lat>
		<long>6.15829</long>
		<climate_hazard>climatological</climate_hazard>
		<project_ID>232487583</project_ID>
		<no_of_images>3</no_of_images>
		<category_of_contribution>solutions_to_adapt_to_climate_</category_of_contribution>
		<extra_links>NA</extra_links>
	</project>
	<project ID="232488483">
		<Name>Claudia</Name>
		<Surname>Larsen</Surname>
		<Affiliation>Chalmers</Affiliation>
		<City_of_Institution>Gothenburg</City_of_Institution>
		<country_001>Sweden</country_001>
		<title_of_project>The Future Times - Speculative Design in Times of Trouble</title_of_project>
		<credits_for_project>Claudia Larsen, Chalmers University of Technology
Maria Oxelman, Chalmers University of Technology
Mario Sommer, Chalmers University of Technology
Weronika Urban, Chalmers University of Technology</credits_for_project>
		<year_of_project>2021</year_of_project>
		<description_of_project>The situation is now critical as 75% of Bangladesh is underwater. Water in Bangladesh has always brought life within the well-balanced monsoon season. However, over the last few years, the seasons are changing, and the tides that once fertilised the soil are now generating death. Climate change is causing The Himalayan glaciers to melt and the sea level to rise. Drinking water is progressively being contaminated, affecting crops, and generating diseases. By the end of the century, the global mean sea level is likely to rise at least 30 cm, and South Asia is predicted to be affected the most. The process cannot be stopped even if the greenhouse gas emissions follow a relatively low pathway in the coming decades. Studies revealed The Sundarbans, the most important ecosystem of the country would be totally lost with one meter rise in sea level. Both the livelihood options of coastal communities and the natural environment of the coastal zone will be affected compromising national stability and food security. Mitigation and adaptation are two options to minimise the impacts. Floating communities could mean a new way of living in the same location, embracing the sea level rise prevents displacement and the disappearance of entire communities.</description_of_project>
		<synopsis_of_project>When building resilience, the community becomes stronger and moves towards an utopian society.</synopsis_of_project>
		<keywords_of_project>sea level rise, floating community, mitigation  adaptation, biomimicry, 3D printing</keywords_of_project>
		<duration_of_solution>long permanent</duration_of_solution>
		<primary_SDG>Climate Action</primary_SDG>
		<secondary_SDG>           Sustainable Cities and Communities,      </secondary_SDG>
		<country_of_contribution>Bangladesh</country_of_contribution>
		<city_of_contribution>Fictional community inspired by the fishing community of Mehendiganj, North of Bhola</city_of_contribution>
		<lat>22.831667</lat>
		<long>90.533333</long>
		<climate_hazard>Hydrological biological</climate_hazard>
		<project_ID>232488483</project_ID>
		<no_of_images>3</no_of_images>
		<category_of_contribution>narrative_of_climate_change___</category_of_contribution>
		<extra_links>NA</extra_links>
	</project>
	<project ID="232501015">
		<Name>Hannah-Fiona</Name>
		<Surname>Steinborn</Surname>
		<Affiliation>Chalmers</Affiliation>
		<City_of_Institution>Gothenburg</City_of_Institution>
		<country_001>Sweden</country_001>
		<title_of_project>Diving deep into the sea of realities</title_of_project>
		<credits_for_project>Lucie Giordano, team member
Maria Elander, team member
Cleo Budde, team member</credits_for_project>
		<year_of_project>2023</year_of_project>
		<description_of_project>The exploitation of land, more specifically the illegal mining of sand, has reached its peak in this case study. Our main character, a fictional tropical island, has been illegally exploited for a long time. It wants to be self-determined again and protect its inhabitants from displacement and the loss of their heritage. What if one day, nature displays its true power and the island decides to sink below the sea level? In our case study we speculate what could happen when nature, which humans are so reliant on but treat so poorly, becomes the most powerful force? ??To find resilience responding to this climate emergency multiverse theory, or the idea of multiple realities played out at the same time, is explored. What if every decision made generates a new reality? Three different universes, three different strategies: Retreat, Adaptation and Regeneration. 
These strategies relate to three different worldviews, retreat being anthropocentric, adaptation more-than-human focused and regeneration became a post human scenario. 
Speculating on these futures also revealed some interconnections, that these timelines intertwine and partly overlap. Although linked, the scenarios deal with very different timeframes and thus touching on the notion of the relativity of time and space.</description_of_project>
		<synopsis_of_project>If nobody acts many beloved islands will become inhabitable due to rising sea levels.</synopsis_of_project>
		<keywords_of_project>flooding, biomimicry, resilience, multiverse, sand-mining</keywords_of_project>
		<duration_of_solution>short long permanent</duration_of_solution>
		<primary_SDG>Climate Action</primary_SDG>
		<secondary_SDG>          Reduced Inequality,  Responsible Consumption and Production,     </secondary_SDG>
		<country_of_contribution>Maldives</country_of_contribution>
		<city_of_contribution>No specific city</city_of_contribution>
		<lat>-6.63187</lat>
		<long>71.385917</long>
		<climate_hazard>climatological Hydrological</climate_hazard>
		<project_ID>232501015</project_ID>
		<no_of_images>3</no_of_images>
		<category_of_contribution>solutions_to_adapt_to_climate_</category_of_contribution>
		<extra_links>NA</extra_links>
	</project>
	<project ID="232538307">
		<Name>Cecilia</Name>
		<Surname>Punzo</Surname>
		<Affiliation>politecnico_di_milano__italy</Affiliation>
		<City_of_Institution>Milan</City_of_Institution>
		<country_001>Italy</country_001>
		<title_of_project>Reborn from water</title_of_project>
		<credits_for_project>Cecilia Punzo, Politecnico di Milano student</credits_for_project>
		<year_of_project>2023</year_of_project>
		<description_of_project>Water, energy, memories, sensitivity. Reborn for water" is made up of all these elements. The project, set in the Le Vene area in Colle Val delsa, combines sustainable and social solutions to adapt to climate change.
The effects that have occurred in this place have resulted in hydrogeological and functional problems in the last ten years, disfiguring the area formed by small channels fed by springs, and leading to the abandonment of the paper mill. 
The goal is to manage flood flows, avoid seabed acidification in the hottest periods and raise awareness among the population, pursuing the principles of the SDGs. In response to all these challenges, the placement of underground water tanks was thought to avoid flooding in case of water bombs and to store excess water and exploit it for various purposes. The positioning of plants on the banks is also envisaged, which help the phytoremediation and a re-stabilization of biodiversity. In addition to this, the entire paper mill complex is also being redesigned to be energy self-sufficient and a place to raise awareness. In this way, the energy produced by the solar panels and the flow of water is recovered, and the use of the structure is permitted with spaces for raising awareness and research activities on climate change.</description_of_project>
		<synopsis_of_project>In some cases we have not utilised the resources (water, wind, sunlight) that used to keep every country in the world alive, in others we have consumed them intensively (the soil). If it is true that man learns from his mistakes, then there is one last hope for our planet.</synopsis_of_project>
		<keywords_of_project>water, sustainable energy production, nature-based-solutions, cultural heritage, innovation hubs</keywords_of_project>
		<duration_of_solution>long</duration_of_solution>
		<primary_SDG>Climate Action</primary_SDG>
		<secondary_SDG>       Clean Water and Sanitation, Affordable and Clean Energy,     Responsible Consumption and Production,     </secondary_SDG>
		<country_of_contribution>Italy</country_of_contribution>
		<city_of_contribution>Colle di Val dElsa</city_of_contribution>
		<lat>43.39284</lat>
		<long>11.11991</long>
		<climate_hazard>Hydrological</climate_hazard>
		<project_ID>232538307</project_ID>
		<no_of_images>3</no_of_images>
		<category_of_contribution>solutions_to_adapt_to_climate_</category_of_contribution>
		<extra_links>NA</extra_links>
	</project>
	<project ID="232765617">
		<Name>Bevan</Name>
		<Surname>Lennox</Surname>
		<Affiliation>other</Affiliation>
		<City_of_Institution>Pretoria</City_of_Institution>
		<country_001>South_Africa</country_001>
		<title_of_project>The stabilization and response strategy of Deborah street</title_of_project>
		<credits_for_project>Mane van der Schijff, BSc Honours (Arch) Student, University of Pretoria
Bevan Lennox, BSc Honours (Arch) Student, University of Pretoria
Cody van Breemen, BSc Honours (Arch) Student, University of Pretoria
Nico Smit, BSc Honours (Arch) Student, University of Pretoria</credits_for_project>
		<year_of_project>2021</year_of_project>
		<description_of_project>The harsh reality of informal settlements are evident in South Africa. The residents living in informal conditions are exposed to a range of risks which can be externally or internally driven. It is believed that some informal settlements and systems will be systematically replaced by formal structures, whilst developmental trends may prove otherwise.

As spatial designers working with urban and spatial development, we have the opportunity to undertake alternative methods to work within these informal contexts whilst utilising appropriate strategies. 

Melusi in the western part of Pretoria, South Africa was set as the case study for the project. Our study aimed at mapping the spatial and material qualities of Melusi, in turn, gaining knowledge on their vulnerabilities. Four categories of vulnerabilities were unpacked namely; Ecology and physical environment, streetscape, socio-economic status quo and identity.
In the end, the objective was to develop high-level streetscape-response strategy addressing the four categories of vulnerabilities in the community. This strategy will aim at lowering the exposure and improve local resilience.</description_of_project>
		<synopsis_of_project>We should work with nature, not against it - David Attenborough</synopsis_of_project>
		<keywords_of_project>Informality, Sustainability, Identity, Streetscape, Ecology</keywords_of_project>
		<duration_of_solution>long</duration_of_solution>
		<primary_SDG>Sustainable Cities and Communities</primary_SDG>
		<secondary_SDG>   Good Health and Well-being,              </secondary_SDG>
		<country_of_contribution>South_Africa</country_of_contribution>
		<city_of_contribution>Pretoria</city_of_contribution>
		<lat>-25.720291</lat>
		<long>28.117326</long>
		<climate_hazard>climatological Hydrological</climate_hazard>
		<project_ID>232765617</project_ID>
		<no_of_images>3</no_of_images>
		<category_of_contribution>solutions_to_adapt_to_climate_</category_of_contribution>
		<extra_links>NA</extra_links>
	</project>
	<project ID="232789266">
		<Name>Cameron</Name>
		<Surname>Forder</Surname>
		<Affiliation>other</Affiliation>
		<City_of_Institution>Pretoria</City_of_Institution>
		<country_001>South_Africa</country_001>
		<title_of_project>Protective prototypes and the clinic at Melusi</title_of_project>
		<credits_for_project>Cameron Forder, University of Pretoria</credits_for_project>
		<year_of_project>2020</year_of_project>
		<description_of_project>Melusi is an informal neighbourhood on the north-western periphery of Tshwane, established as the result of vast immigration by those seeking jobs in the metropolitan centre. 
Its rapid expansion has not been met with adequate public 
services, and as a result, its residents are particularly vulnerable to external change. 
Unsupported, residents lack sufficient access to healthcare and 
information, and future-safe housing and public space. 
This project looks at developing architectural prototypes to address the communities climate and long-term protection.</description_of_project>
		<synopsis_of_project>There is hope in our innate desire to collaborate</synopsis_of_project>
		<keywords_of_project>Prototype, Protective, agency, education, passive</keywords_of_project>
		<duration_of_solution>long</duration_of_solution>
		<primary_SDG>Sustainable Cities and Communities</primary_SDG>
		<secondary_SDG>   Good Health and Well-being,              </secondary_SDG>
		<country_of_contribution>South_Africa</country_of_contribution>
		<city_of_contribution>Pretoria</city_of_contribution>
		<lat>-25.782531</lat>
		<long>28.26107</long>
		<climate_hazard>climatological</climate_hazard>
		<project_ID>232789266</project_ID>
		<no_of_images>3</no_of_images>
		<category_of_contribution>solutions_to_adapt_to_climate_</category_of_contribution>
		<extra_links>NA</extra_links>
	</project>
	<project ID="232791089">
		<Name>Erpinio</Name>
		<Surname>Labrozzi</Surname>
		<Affiliation>politecnico_di_milano__italy</Affiliation>
		<City_of_Institution>Milan</City_of_Institution>
		<country_001>Italy</country_001>
		<title_of_project>Cobalt blue</title_of_project>
		<credits_for_project>Erpinio Labrozzi, Politecnico di Milano, ABC Department
Federico Godino
Mattia Tettoni - Universita IUAV di Venezia
Alessandro De Vita
Filippo Tartaglia
Luigi Tredicine - Universita di Ferrara</credits_for_project>
		<year_of_project>2023</year_of_project>
		<description_of_project>The video essay investigates the trans-scalar relationships and the environmental and social impacts embodied in consumer electronics and automotive. In particular, the project examines global, continental (Europe), and local (Piedmont-Italy), flows and extraction dynamics of cobalt.
The use of cobalt in lithium-ion batteries makes this material crucial for the environmental transition while at the same time being responsible for habitat and biodiversity loss, soil erosion, water pollution, labor exploitation, and cycles of violence, especially in developing countries such as Democratic Republic of Congo (DRC).
A 3D animation and other data visualization render the flows of the material on a global scale and the geopolitical dynamics of the phenomena, with the DRC and China being, respectively, the leading exporter and primary importer of the mineral.
A renewed interest in the European Union for cobalt extraction from indigenous sources is demonstrated by maps and video content at the continental scale.
In particular, in the Western Alps, in the municipalities of Usseglio and Balme (Italy), new plans are in place for mineral extraction. Will this activity be compatible with strategies for sensibly using mountain ecosystems?</description_of_project>
		<synopsis_of_project>Scenarios must be proposed to respond to the climate emergency without further damaging the ecosystem and local communities in developing countries</synopsis_of_project>
		<keywords_of_project>Resources, mining, exploitment, operational landscapes, rare earths</keywords_of_project>
		<duration_of_solution>permanent</duration_of_solution>
		<primary_SDG>Responsible Consumption and Production</primary_SDG>
		<secondary_SDG>   Good Health and Well-being,      Industry, Innovation and Infrastructure,        </secondary_SDG>
		<country_of_contribution>Italy</country_of_contribution>
		<city_of_contribution>Usseglio</city_of_contribution>
		<lat>45.233594</lat>
		<long>7.218427</long>
		<climate_hazard>geophysical</climate_hazard>
		<project_ID>232791089</project_ID>
		<no_of_images>3</no_of_images>
		<category_of_contribution>narrative_of_climate_change___</category_of_contribution>
		<extra_links>https://www.youtu.be/1KhsjlG6sjs</extra_links>
	</project>
	<project ID="232999155">
		<Name>David</Name>
		<Surname>Schulte-Ladbeck</Surname>
		<Affiliation>rwth_aachen__germany</Affiliation>
		<City_of_Institution>Aachen</City_of_Institution>
		<country_001>Germany</country_001>
		<title_of_project>The architect changemaker</title_of_project>
		<credits_for_project>The Project is a work of David Schulte-Ladbeck, Marie Lintel and Jessica Bill

It was created within the architectural Master Study at:

act of building 
Junior Professorship of Construction and Design
Faculty of Architecture RWTH Aachen University
actofbuilding_rwth
www.actofbuilding.rwth-aachen.de</credits_for_project>
		<year_of_project>2022</year_of_project>
		<description_of_project>As described at the website:

New times, New Heroes!
 
The earth is a closed system, and our stay on the Planet earth  is only temporary. The climate crisis is confronting current societies with radical transformations with tangible and non-tangible consequences in all aspects of life; from the social, the economic, the cultural, the natural to the building environment. Changes, big and small, radical and modest, are needed to rethink, prepare, envisage and manage the resulting complexity of society towards sustainable and convivial survival of mankind on a thriving planet. To do this, agents are needed to be the drivers of these changes. We wish therefore to rewrite the definition of the architect to match our current challenges and become more of a changemaker.
 
The studio the architect-changemaker looks towards the pre-industrialised concept of the master builder. It reflects the idea of an integral approach to architecture, embedded in local context, local materials and local craftsmanship. We are in search for a new type of architect rather than a new type of architecture. In close collaboration with the hybrid practice of BC architects  studies  materials, the student will research within the Euregion Maas-Rhine potentially circular flows, develop samples of new geo-sourced materials, design a folly with a chosen new material and finally develop a larger narrative and prototype it on scale 1:1 within a workshop setting.</description_of_project>
		<synopsis_of_project>Finding better ways to create a better earth for all to live on</synopsis_of_project>
		<keywords_of_project>sustainable architecture, reuse everything, rammed earth construction, geo-based materials, Carbon neutrality</keywords_of_project>
		<duration_of_solution>short long</duration_of_solution>
		<primary_SDG>Climate Action</primary_SDG>
		<secondary_SDG>            Responsible Consumption and Production,     </secondary_SDG>
		<country_of_contribution>Germany</country_of_contribution>
		<city_of_contribution>Aachen</city_of_contribution>
		<lat>50.931326</lat>
		<long>5.848446</long>
		<climate_hazard>climatological</climate_hazard>
		<project_ID>232999155</project_ID>
		<no_of_images>3</no_of_images>
		<category_of_contribution>solutions_to_adapt_to_climate_</category_of_contribution>
		<extra_links>NA</extra_links>
	</project>
	<project ID="233055268">
		<Name>Ban Liang</Name>
		<Surname>Ling</Surname>
		<Affiliation>singapore_university_of_technology_and_d</Affiliation>
		<City_of_Institution>Singapore</City_of_Institution>
		<country_001>Singapore</country_001>
		<title_of_project>Thermal comfort in singapore</title_of_project>
		<credits_for_project>Ban Liang Ling</credits_for_project>
		<year_of_project>2023</year_of_project>
		<description_of_project>Life in Singapore is warm with the odd bit of torrential downpour. We always hope for a steady stream of wind flow so that we can reduce the reliance on air conditioning. In that sense the urban landscape has been kind, providing shelters from the sun and rain. The contribution highlights ways that one can use to further improve ones thermal comfort. Customising it to reduce the reliance on machine usage.</description_of_project>
		<synopsis_of_project>Better designed residential areas that limit damage to the environment</synopsis_of_project>
		<keywords_of_project>Thermal, comfort, tropical</keywords_of_project>
		<duration_of_solution>long</duration_of_solution>
		<primary_SDG>Sustainable Cities and Communities</primary_SDG>
		<secondary_SDG>       Affordable and Clean Energy,          </secondary_SDG>
		<country_of_contribution>Singapore</country_of_contribution>
		<city_of_contribution>Singapore</city_of_contribution>
		<lat>1.331074</lat>
		<long>103.896908</long>
		<climate_hazard>meteorological</climate_hazard>
		<project_ID>233055268</project_ID>
		<no_of_images>3</no_of_images>
		<category_of_contribution>solutions_to_adapt_to_climate_</category_of_contribution>
		<extra_links>NA</extra_links>
	</project>
	<project ID="233056273">
		<Name>Nicholas</Name>
		<Surname>Lim</Surname>
		<Affiliation>singapore_university_of_technology_and_d</Affiliation>
		<City_of_Institution>Singapore</City_of_Institution>
		<country_001>Singapore</country_001>
		<title_of_project>Dispositions of Oil</title_of_project>
		<credits_for_project>Nicholas Lim</credits_for_project>
		<year_of_project>2022</year_of_project>
		<description_of_project>The project starts with a rabid critique to oil addiction and the anthropocentric forms of inhabiting the planet, manifested in a speculative Asian Coalition centered around biofuel within the Spratly Islands. Without subverting contemporary intuitions of control and exhausted paradigms of power, any post-oil future becomes a similar addiction. Thus, the thesis revolves around counterintuitive practices that reject ontological assumption of human superiority in favor of negotiating non-human agencies, to reach a new performative and emergent nature way of collaborative survival in a time of massive uncertainty.</description_of_project>
		<synopsis_of_project>it is about counterintuitive practices that reject ontological assumption of human superiority in favor of negotiating non-human agencies, to reach a new performative and emergent nature way of collaborative survival in a time of massive uncertainty.</synopsis_of_project>
		<keywords_of_project>sustainability</keywords_of_project>
		<duration_of_solution>long</duration_of_solution>
		<primary_SDG>Affordable and Clean Energy</primary_SDG>
		<secondary_SDG>             Climate Action,    </secondary_SDG>
		<country_of_contribution>China</country_of_contribution>
		<city_of_contribution>all country</city_of_contribution>
		<lat>31.503629</lat>
		<long>113.190153</long>
		<climate_hazard>geophysical</climate_hazard>
		<project_ID>233056273</project_ID>
		<no_of_images>3</no_of_images>
		<category_of_contribution>solutions_to_adapt_to_climate_</category_of_contribution>
		<extra_links>https://www.asd.sutd.edu.sg/gradshow/march/projects/2022/nicholas-lim/</extra_links>
	</project>
	<project ID="233068279">
		<Name>Megan</Name>
		<Surname>Moktar</Surname>
		<Affiliation>singapore_university_of_technology_and_d</Affiliation>
		<City_of_Institution>Singapore</City_of_Institution>
		<country_001>Singapore</country_001>
		<title_of_project>Second Cycles: Synthesis of Techno-Natures</title_of_project>
		<credits_for_project>Megan Riri Moktar</credits_for_project>
		<year_of_project>2022</year_of_project>
		<description_of_project>Speculating the future of current informal e-waste communities within the larger regional setting of recycling and upcycling industry, in an ever-changing technological landscape</description_of_project>
		<synopsis_of_project>Speculating the future of current informal e-waste communities within the larger regional setting of recycling and upcycling industry, in an ever-changing technological landscape</synopsis_of_project>
		<keywords_of_project>waste management, sustainability</keywords_of_project>
		<duration_of_solution>long</duration_of_solution>
		<primary_SDG>Climate Action</primary_SDG>
		<secondary_SDG>         Industry, Innovation and Infrastructure,   Responsible Consumption and Production,     </secondary_SDG>
		<country_of_contribution>Thailand</country_of_contribution>
		<city_of_contribution>na</city_of_contribution>
		<lat>7.564673</lat>
		<long>99.369842</long>
		<climate_hazard>climatological</climate_hazard>
		<project_ID>233068279</project_ID>
		<no_of_images>2</no_of_images>
		<category_of_contribution>solutions_to_adapt_to_climate_</category_of_contribution>
		<extra_links>https://www.asd.sutd.edu.sg/gradshow/march/projects/2022/megan-moktar/</extra_links>
	</project>
	<project ID="233074459">
		<Name>Ben</Name>
		<Surname>Jooste</Surname>
		<Affiliation>university_of_pretoria</Affiliation>
		<City_of_Institution>Pretoria</City_of_Institution>
		<country_001>South_Africa</country_001>
		<title_of_project>Addressing ownership vulnerability through the development of spatial nodes</title_of_project>
		<credits_for_project>Ben Jooste, student
Melicia van Loggerenberg, student
Sam Steyn, student
Michael Read, student</credits_for_project>
		<year_of_project>2021</year_of_project>
		<description_of_project>This project was an investigation into the vulnerability of the informal settlement of Melusi 2 in Pretoria West. The first step was to map different types of vulnerability found in the settlement, and through analysis aided by theoretical material from Jaime Hernandez-Garcia, Seth Asara Okyere, Jan Gehl, and others, we identified that the principles of ownership, accessibility, and intersubjectivity are the most prominent features of this settlement, and through these, it is possible to alleviate the infrastructural vulnerability of Melusi 2, which is based on its process-based development. Using the aforementioned principles, by intervening in catalytical nodes, specifically spaces of semi-publicsemi-privatecommunal areas such as the water tanks, we can deal with the most extreme vulnerability: ownership, and use a bottom-up feedback-loop strategy that informs itself as it succeeds or not, being sensitive to current systems and people.</description_of_project>
		<synopsis_of_project>"People are at the center of the social production of space in informal settlements. The participation of the people in the transformation of their own environment is paramount" (Hernandez-Garcia, 2013): intersubjectivity like this is key in understanding not only informal settlements, but in approaching climate change issues.</synopsis_of_project>
		<keywords_of_project>informal settlement, climate change, vulnerability, mapping, ownership</keywords_of_project>
		<duration_of_solution>long</duration_of_solution>
		<primary_SDG>Industry, Innovation and Infrastructure</primary_SDG>
		<secondary_SDG>       Clean Water and Sanitation,      Responsible Consumption and Production,     Partnerships to achieve the Goal,</secondary_SDG>
		<country_of_contribution>South_Africa</country_of_contribution>
		<city_of_contribution>Pretoria</city_of_contribution>
		<lat>-25.724363</lat>
		<long>28.124433</long>
		<climate_hazard>climatological Hydrological</climate_hazard>
		<project_ID>233074459</project_ID>
		<no_of_images>3</no_of_images>
		<category_of_contribution>solutions_to_adapt_to_climate_</category_of_contribution>
		<extra_links>NA</extra_links>
	</project>
	<project ID="233147581">
		<Name>Yukun</Name>
		<Surname>Wang</Surname>
		<Affiliation>singapore_university_of_technology_and_d</Affiliation>
		<City_of_Institution>Singapore</City_of_Institution>
		<country_001>Singapore</country_001>
		<title_of_project>Climate Change</title_of_project>
		<credits_for_project>Wang Yukun</credits_for_project>
		<year_of_project>2023</year_of_project>
		<description_of_project>Personal experience and insights relating to climate change</description_of_project>
		<synopsis_of_project>Hopefully, mankind will maximize their efforts on improving climate conditions.</synopsis_of_project>
		<keywords_of_project>climate change, impact, solution</keywords_of_project>
		<duration_of_solution>short</duration_of_solution>
		<primary_SDG>Climate Action</primary_SDG>
		<secondary_SDG>
		</secondary_SDG>
		<country_of_contribution>Singapore</country_of_contribution>
		<city_of_contribution>Singapore</city_of_contribution>
		<lat>1.349072</lat>
		<long>103.865177</long>
		<climate_hazard>meteorological</climate_hazard>
		<project_ID>233147581</project_ID>
		<no_of_images>1</no_of_images>
		<category_of_contribution>narrative_of_climate_change___</category_of_contribution>
		<extra_links>NA</extra_links>
	</project>
	<project ID="233178819">
		<Name>Christian</Name>
		<Surname>Holscher</Surname>
		<Affiliation>rwth_aachen__germany</Affiliation>
		<City_of_Institution>Aachen</City_of_Institution>
		<country_001>Germany</country_001>
		<title_of_project>Regionale 2025 Zanders Areal Bergisch Gladbach</title_of_project>
		<credits_for_project>Christian Holscher</credits_for_project>
		<year_of_project>2023</year_of_project>
		<description_of_project>The city of Bergisch Gladbach was shaped by the paper industry. The area of the Zanders paper mill is located in the middle of the city. This was closed. The project deals with the transformation of a former paper mill into a piece of the city. The construction sector is responsible for 38 of global energy-related CO-2 emissions. The project is intended to show a way of how the sustainable use of existing buildings and the reuse of building materials can work.</description_of_project>
		<synopsis_of_project>Every existing building already has its carbon footprint</synopsis_of_project>
		<keywords_of_project>Sustainable Cities, ReUse,  historical heritage, housing shortage</keywords_of_project>
		<duration_of_solution>permanent</duration_of_solution>
		<primary_SDG>Sustainable Cities and Communities</primary_SDG>
		<secondary_SDG>         Industry, Innovation and Infrastructure,  Sustainable Cities and Communities, Responsible Consumption and Production, Climate Action,    </secondary_SDG>
		<country_of_contribution>Germany</country_of_contribution>
		<city_of_contribution>Bergisch Gladbach</city_of_contribution>
		<lat>50.986983</lat>
		<long>7.128001</long>
		<climate_hazard>meteorological</climate_hazard>
		<project_ID>233178819</project_ID>
		<no_of_images>3</no_of_images>
		<category_of_contribution>solutions_to_adapt_to_climate_</category_of_contribution>
		<extra_links>NA</extra_links>
	</project>
	<project ID="233233228">
		<Name>Kateryna</Name>
		<Surname>Konieva</Surname>
		<Affiliation>singapore_university_of_technology_and_d</Affiliation>
		<City_of_Institution>Singapore</City_of_Institution>
		<country_001>Singapore</country_001>
		<title_of_project>War and climate change</title_of_project>
		<credits_for_project>Kateryna Konieva, SUTD</credits_for_project>
		<year_of_project>2023</year_of_project>
		<description_of_project>With all the possible headlines on the Russian invasion of Ukraine, there is little attention and little numbers on its effect on the environment. This tremendous contributor to the climate change is being overlooked and understudied, in large part due to the lack of the real-time data. In this video I will summarize the major types of the environmental damage caused by the war, and provide the numbers to compare its CO2 emissions to the regular commercial flights. 

You might be surprised to know that several years of the war can cross out the CO2 "credits" saved during no-flight COVID19 period. You might also not know that the animal migration patterns are affected by the military activity, and current global food security risk is directly tied to the environmental destructions on the Ukrainian farmlands. 

This video is not only the list of facts, but also the call to stay informed and not let such major climate change contributions slip your attention.</description_of_project>
		<synopsis_of_project>Climate-specific problems sometimes require non-climate specific solutions.</synopsis_of_project>
		<keywords_of_project>emissions, war, fires, food security, nuclear security</keywords_of_project>
		<duration_of_solution>long</duration_of_solution>
		<primary_SDG>Climate Action</primary_SDG>
		<secondary_SDG>  Zero Hunger,         Sustainable Cities and Communities,     Peace and Justice Strong Institutions, </secondary_SDG>
		<country_of_contribution>Ukraine</country_of_contribution>
		<city_of_contribution>Kyiv</city_of_contribution>
		<lat>50.450833</lat>
		<long>30.522942</long>
		<climate_hazard>climatological</climate_hazard>
		<project_ID>233233228</project_ID>
		<no_of_images>3</no_of_images>
		<category_of_contribution>narrative_of_climate_change___</category_of_contribution>
		<extra_links>https://www.instagram.com/p/Cq6ju0DgdZ1/</extra_links>
	</project>
	<project ID="233289279">
		<Name>Iryna</Name>
		<Surname>Vakulyk</Surname>
		<Affiliation>rwth_aachen__germany</Affiliation>
		<City_of_Institution>Aachen</City_of_Institution>
		<country_001>Germany</country_001>
		<title_of_project>Climate Catastrophe hits the poorest countries the hardest</title_of_project>
		<credits_for_project>Iryna Vakulyk, M.Sc. Transforming City Regions</credits_for_project>
		<year_of_project>2023</year_of_project>
		<description_of_project>I tell a personal story about how my team and I witnessed the consequences of climate change in Haiti. It is known, that the countries of the Global South suffer from climate change way more than the wealthier ones. 
Freshwater deficiency (during the rainy season, which is alarming!) could have not only led to the death of crops, which are crucial for survival but would also mean poorer hygienic conditions, which could end with the outbreak of cholera, typhus and other dangerous diseases. For the local citizens, in a country without a functioning water supply, vaccines and other luxuries of civilization, the consequences could have been severe.</description_of_project>
		<synopsis_of_project>The Global North has a duty to help the developing countries help themselves fight climate change</synopsis_of_project>
		<keywords_of_project>development cooperation, education, resilience</keywords_of_project>
		<duration_of_solution>long</duration_of_solution>
		<primary_SDG>Quality Education</primary_SDG>
		<secondary_SDG> No Poverty, Zero Hunger,     Clean Water and Sanitation, Affordable and Clean Energy,    Sustainable Cities and Communities,      Partnerships to achieve the Goal,</secondary_SDG>
		<country_of_contribution>Haiti</country_of_contribution>
		<city_of_contribution>Beaumont</city_of_contribution>
		<lat>18.478776</lat>
		<long>-73.965226</long>
		<climate_hazard>climatological geophysical biological</climate_hazard>
		<project_ID>233289279</project_ID>
		<no_of_images>3</no_of_images>
		<category_of_contribution>narrative_of_climate_change___</category_of_contribution>
		<extra_links>https://www.irynavakulyk.art/engineers-without-b orders-in-haiti-en/</extra_links>
	</project>
	<project ID="233332828">
		<Name>Tessa</Name>
		<Surname>van Mourik</Surname>
		<Affiliation>tu_delft__the_netherlands</Affiliation>
		<City_of_Institution>TU Delft</City_of_Institution>
		<country_001>Netherlands</country_001>
		<title_of_project>Sustainability TU Delft</title_of_project>
		<credits_for_project>Andy van den Dobbelsteen - Sustainability Project Coordinator
Deirdre van Gameren - Sustainability Project Coordinator
Monika Roeling - Researcher Education 
Hans Suijkerbuijk - Policy  governance
Hubert Linssen - Campus Real Estate
Stijn van Boxmeer - Policy  governance
Puck Wijnia - Chair GreenTU 
Tessa van Mourik - Communications</credits_for_project>
		<year_of_project>2019</year_of_project>
		<description_of_project>TU Delft aims to be CO2-neutral, climate-adaptive and circular, with contribution to the quality of life and biodiversity, by 2030. We focus on all aspects that affects our climate and the environment: from buildings and energy systems to waste management and mobility.</description_of_project>
		<synopsis_of_project>We hope to be an example for other organisations in society to become carbon neutral, climate adaptive and circular.</synopsis_of_project>
		<keywords_of_project>Sustainable University, living labs, susatinable education, biodiversity and life quality</keywords_of_project>
		<duration_of_solution>long</duration_of_solution>
		<primary_SDG>Sustainable Cities and Communities</primary_SDG>
		<secondary_SDG>         Industry, Innovation and Infrastructure,  Sustainable Cities and Communities, Responsible Consumption and Production,     </secondary_SDG>
		<country_of_contribution>Netherlands</country_of_contribution>
		<city_of_contribution>Delft</city_of_contribution>
		<lat>52.002716</lat>
		<long>4.375272</long>
		<climate_hazard>meteorological climatological</climate_hazard>
		<project_ID>233332828</project_ID>
		<no_of_images>1</no_of_images>
		<category_of_contribution>solutions_to_adapt_to_climate_</category_of_contribution>
		<extra_links>https://www.tudelft.nl/en/sustainability</extra_links>
	</project>
	<project ID="233415557">
		<Name>Yohei</Name>
		<Surname>Kato</Surname>
		<Affiliation>singapore_university_of_technology_and_d</Affiliation>
		<City_of_Institution>Singapore</City_of_Institution>
		<country_001>Singapore</country_001>
		<title_of_project>Building Community Resilience: How Japanese Neighborhoods Address Climate Change</title_of_project>
		<credits_for_project>Yohei Kato, Ph.D. Candidate, Singapore University of Technology and Design</credits_for_project>
		<year_of_project>2023</year_of_project>
		<description_of_project>The video explores experiences in Japan and how people work together to cope with the impact of climate change. It highlights the specialized committees in many neighborhoods that educate people on natural disasters and how to prepare for them. By sharing knowledge and resources, people learn to work together to develop strategies to deal with climate change. The video emphasizes the power of community in addressing the challenges posed by climate change, allowing people to better prepare for and respond to the impacts of a changing climate.</description_of_project>
		<synopsis_of_project>The power of community and collaboration in addressing the impact of climate change</synopsis_of_project>
		<keywords_of_project>community engagement, resilience, awareness raising, Japan, extreme weather</keywords_of_project>
		<duration_of_solution>long</duration_of_solution>
		<primary_SDG>Climate Action</primary_SDG>
		<secondary_SDG>           Sustainable Cities and Communities,      </secondary_SDG>
		<country_of_contribution>Japan</country_of_contribution>
		<city_of_contribution>West Tokyo</city_of_contribution>
		<lat>35.74578</lat>
		<long>139.534516</long>
		<climate_hazard>meteorological</climate_hazard>
		<project_ID>233415557</project_ID>
		<no_of_images>1</no_of_images>
		<category_of_contribution>narrative_of_climate_change___</category_of_contribution>
		<extra_links>NA</extra_links>
	</project>
	<project ID="233505210">
		<Name>Ibtsam</Name>
		<Surname>Saeed</Surname>
		<Affiliation>rwth_aachen__germany</Affiliation>
		<City_of_Institution>Aachen</City_of_Institution>
		<country_001>Germany</country_001>
		<title_of_project>Integrated Project II - Eco Tourism</title_of_project>
		<credits_for_project>Ibtsam Saeed,
Enes Kac,
Shaily,
Zainab Chaudhry</credits_for_project>
		<year_of_project>2022</year_of_project>
		<description_of_project>Istanbul went through an amazingly rapid industrialisation process. The speed and scale of this urbanization depends on the built environment and affect the natural environment. The stone material which is the basic necessity for the built environment of the city, has been provided from the stone quarry areas surrounding the city. However, today these stone quarry areas are squeezed not only in the forestsgreen Landscapes but also near the Urban and Rural settlement areas. These smoke
covered infertile landscapes are having adverse effects on the surrounding, the people as well as the biodiversity. The Studies are evident and produce the fact that eco-tourism has the potential to create beneficial effects on the environment by contributing to environmental protection and conservation. It is a way to restore the balance and raise awareness of environmental values, and it can serve as a tool to finance protection of natural areas and increase their economic importance. 

This Project focuses on introducing and proposing Eco-Tourism as a key opportunity and strength in Revitalization of the Quarries of the Peninsula. Adopting the learnings from the detailed Analysis, we aim to present our vision for these Quarries in relation to the surroundings and the impact it will have on the climate, biodiversity and the people in the following years.</description_of_project>
		<synopsis_of_project>Hope: Eco tourism can promote conservation and awareness for a sustainable future.</synopsis_of_project>
		<keywords_of_project>Environmental Protection, Community empowerment, Economy, Education, Cultural interaction.</keywords_of_project>
		<duration_of_solution>long</duration_of_solution>
		<primary_SDG>Life on Land</primary_SDG>
		<secondary_SDG>           Sustainable Cities and Communities,  Climate Action,    Partnerships to achieve the Goal,</secondary_SDG>
		<country_of_contribution>Turkey</country_of_contribution>
		<city_of_contribution>Istanbul</city_of_contribution>
		<lat>41.12359</lat>
		<long>28.870268</long>
		<climate_hazard>meteorological climatological Hydrological</climate_hazard>
		<project_ID>233505210</project_ID>
		<no_of_images>1</no_of_images>
		<category_of_contribution>solutions_to_adapt_to_climate_</category_of_contribution>
		<extra_links>https://www.issuu.com/ibtsamsaeed/docs/ip_report_eco-tourism</extra_links>
	</project>
	<project ID="233552315">
		<Name>Ekaterina</Name>
		<Surname>Plekhanova</Surname>
		<Affiliation>rwth_aachen__germany</Affiliation>
		<City_of_Institution>Aachen</City_of_Institution>
		<country_001>Germany</country_001>
		<title_of_project>From Wave to Circle: Evaluation and Circular Economy Strategy Development in Industrial Port Areas on the Case Study of Duisburg Port</title_of_project>
		<credits_for_project>Wasila Parvez</credits_for_project>
		<year_of_project>2023</year_of_project>
		<description_of_project>This work addresses the circular economy challenges in the port areas. The thesis suggests a strategy for evaluation of the current circular transition stage and develops a building blocks framework in order to promote circular economy development in port areas.
Ports provide a crucial influence on the cities they are located in, and it is essential to perceive ports as trendsetters, which reveals the relevance of the suggested topic. A port being a catalyst of transition can initiate the change of the urban and regional settings. The building blocks are seen to facilitate circular development within the ports and therefore provide impact on the cities they are located in. This project proposes an analytical approach for categorizing circular initiatives within port areas and evaluating the circular economy level in ports. Based on the evaluation, the building blocks framework is developed as a tool for encouraging the circular transition via spatial and non-spatial tools and interventions. This project aims to develop a circular economy strategy for port areas which can be implemented with some minor adjustments for diverse ports of local and regional importance. The implementation of the strategy will be presented on the example of the port of Duisburg.</description_of_project>
		<synopsis_of_project>Recourses of our planet are limited and therefore require preservation.</synopsis_of_project>
		<keywords_of_project>circular economy, cities, ports, transition, Duisburg</keywords_of_project>
		<duration_of_solution>short long permanent</duration_of_solution>
		<primary_SDG>Sustainable Cities and Communities</primary_SDG>
		<secondary_SDG>   Good Health and Well-being,    Clean Water and Sanitation,   Industry, Innovation and Infrastructure,   Responsible Consumption and Production, Climate Action,    Partnerships to achieve the Goal,</secondary_SDG>
		<country_of_contribution>Germany</country_of_contribution>
		<city_of_contribution>Duisburg</city_of_contribution>
		<lat>51.450129</lat>
		<long>6.747425</long>
		<climate_hazard>meteorological Hydrological</climate_hazard>
		<project_ID>233552315</project_ID>
		<no_of_images>3</no_of_images>
		<category_of_contribution>solutions_to_adapt_to_climate_</category_of_contribution>
		<extra_links>NA</extra_links>
	</project>
	<project ID="233568557">
		<Name>Wasila</Name>
		<Surname>Parvez</Surname>
		<Affiliation>rwth_aachen__germany</Affiliation>
		<City_of_Institution>Aachen</City_of_Institution>
		<country_001>Germany</country_001>
		<title_of_project>Resilient Landscape</title_of_project>
		<credits_for_project>Shivani Handa, colleague
Said Kocak, colleague</credits_for_project>
		<year_of_project>2022</year_of_project>
		<description_of_project>Deteriorating landscapes are becoming a major worldwide issue. In particular, this research looks into such landscapes in Istanbul, Turkey, where mining activities have grown more prominent and now account for a sizable portion of urban expansion. With an emphasis on the quarries in the Cendere, Cebeci, and atalca districts, the project investigates how peri-urban and rural landscapes might be transformed into robust and community-oriented environments. Landscape resilience is envisioned as a social, ecological, economic, and infrastructural network that is interrelated.

This researchs main goal is to suggest a paradigm change from a profit-driven economy to an environmentally centred development model that puts local community wellbeing first. The project aims to create a sustainable framework that promotes environmental preservation, social harmony, and economic diversification through the renovation of the aforementioned quarries. This study adds to the body of knowledge on resilient landscapes, community development, and sustainable urban design in areas that are quickly urbanising by using an interdisciplinary approach.</description_of_project>
		<synopsis_of_project>Landscape resilience may help create sustainable communities, which can help to lessen the effects of climate change and protect the future of our planet.</synopsis_of_project>
		<keywords_of_project>Landscape Resilience, Sustainable Urban Planning, Ecologically Centered Growth, Community Development, Quarry Redevelopment</keywords_of_project>
		<duration_of_solution>long</duration_of_solution>
		<primary_SDG>Climate Action</primary_SDG>
		<secondary_SDG>       Affordable and Clean Energy,  Industry, Innovation and Infrastructure,  Sustainable Cities and Communities,      </secondary_SDG>
		<country_of_contribution>Turkey</country_of_contribution>
		<city_of_contribution>Istanbul</city_of_contribution>
		<lat>41.143353</lat>
		<long>28.461087</long>
		<climate_hazard>climatological</climate_hazard>
		<project_ID>233568557</project_ID>
		<no_of_images>1</no_of_images>
		<category_of_contribution>solutions_to_adapt_to_climate_</category_of_contribution>
		<extra_links>NA</extra_links>
	</project>
	<project ID="233584929">
		<Name>Ben</Name>
		<Surname>Pleininger</Surname>
		<Affiliation>rwth_aachen__germany</Affiliation>
		<City_of_Institution>Aachen</City_of_Institution>
		<country_001>Germany</country_001>
		<title_of_project>Jecken am Werk</title_of_project>
		<credits_for_project>Wilma Heitmann, cand. B.Sc. RWTH Aachen
Svea Friesenhahn, cand. B.Sc. RWTH Aachen
Tim Christ, cand. B.Sc. RWTH Aachen
Manuel Wolf, cand. B.Sc. RWTH Aachen
Ben Pleininger, cand. B.Sc. RWTH Aachen</credits_for_project>
		<year_of_project>2023</year_of_project>
		<description_of_project>On Aachens historic site known as "Elf Jecken", the socially just and climate-sensitive neighbourhood of the Jecken am Werk is planned as part of a semester long research process. Historically significant as an industrial site, the conversion to a healthy mixed-use area of new and old residents alike was anticipated. In order to harmonise the urban grain of large-scale commercial halls with small-scale residential and mixed-use structures a finely woven network of lush green courtyards, public squares and moderately sealed areas of movement is to characterise the quarter. In spatial terms, the proposed project can be described as a hybrid of courtyard and block typologies, which are oriented towards existing structures wherever suitable to further enhance the build up of place-related identities. As a local backbone, the prolonged Liebigstrabe should connect the existing cultural quarter in the north of Julicher Strabe with recreation spaces along the river Wurm and offer high qualities and everyday-services to existing residents. New forms of housing and the demand to create living space, especially for neglected population groups, lead to a creative mix of buildings and find expression in the heterogeneity of the built environment.</description_of_project>
		<synopsis_of_project>Transformation of an industrial area into an urban environmentally friendly urban quarters, which reacts sensitively to existing conditions and finds answers to current questions of climate protection.</synopsis_of_project>
		<keywords_of_project>Renaturation, climate-friendly construction, Protecting existing buildings, Transformation, Micro organisms</keywords_of_project>
		<duration_of_solution>long</duration_of_solution>
		<primary_SDG>Sustainable Cities and Communities</primary_SDG>
		<secondary_SDG>         Industry, Innovation and Infrastructure,   Responsible Consumption and Production,     </secondary_SDG>
		<country_of_contribution>Germany</country_of_contribution>
		<city_of_contribution>Aachen</city_of_contribution>
		<lat>50.78908</lat>
		<long>6.11757</long>
		<climate_hazard>biological</climate_hazard>
		<project_ID>233584929</project_ID>
		<no_of_images>3</no_of_images>
		<category_of_contribution>solutions_to_adapt_to_climate_</category_of_contribution>
		<extra_links>NA</extra_links>
	</project>
	<project ID="233618438">
		<Name>Benedict</Name>
		<Surname>Tan</Surname>
		<Affiliation>singapore_university_of_technology_and_d</Affiliation>
		<City_of_Institution>Singapore</City_of_Institution>
		<country_001>Singapore</country_001>
		<title_of_project>To Mother Nature: Planetary Governance through the Permafrost</title_of_project>
		<credits_for_project>Benedict Tan</credits_for_project>
		<year_of_project>2021</year_of_project>
		<description_of_project>The project seeks to redefine what it means to be sustainable through the management of the permafrost. Ideas of hyperintelligence and planetary governance are introduced as new forms of understanding the nature that we inhabit. 

Most would agree about the need to have sustainability, but what it means to each person differs. The phenomena of sustainability shows that it is insufficient to merely rely on human perception and understanding to solve issues that are beyond our lived reality. There is a need to first describe the problem that faces us as close to its totality as possible, before organising our efforts to confront it.</description_of_project>
		<synopsis_of_project>The project seeks to redefine what it means to be sustainable through the management of the permafrost.</synopsis_of_project>
		<keywords_of_project>Planetary Governance, Rig, Sustainability</keywords_of_project>
		<duration_of_solution>long</duration_of_solution>
		<primary_SDG> Clean Water and Sanitation</primary_SDG>
		<secondary_SDG>   Good Health and Well-being,    Affordable and Clean Energy,  Industry, Innovation and Infrastructure,        </secondary_SDG>
		<country_of_contribution>Singapore</country_of_contribution>
		<city_of_contribution>singapore</city_of_contribution>
		<lat>72.289067</lat>
		<long>40.020081</long>
		<climate_hazard>climatological</climate_hazard>
		<project_ID>233618438</project_ID>
		<no_of_images>3</no_of_images>
		<category_of_contribution>solutions_to_adapt_to_climate_</category_of_contribution>
		<extra_links>https://www.asd.sutd.edu.sg/gradshow/march/projects/2021/benedict-tan/</extra_links>
	</project>
	<project ID="233620276">
		<Name>Poon Weng</Name>
		<Surname>Shern</Surname>
		<Affiliation>singapore_university_of_technology_and_d</Affiliation>
		<City_of_Institution>singapore</City_of_Institution>
		<country_001>Singapore</country_001>
		<title_of_project>Re(Polder)-gramming:  The discretization of mammoth infrastructure</title_of_project>
		<credits_for_project>Poon Weng Shern</credits_for_project>
		<year_of_project>2020</year_of_project>
		<description_of_project>My thesis project touches base on 3 key issues that seek to assess and reflect on the times that we live in. 
 [Climate] Crisis. The world is plunging into a state of crisis, yet people do not seem to take these concerns seriously. Sea level rise are about to put millions of people without land, yet we carry on as if this will not happen. 
 Poldering. (the diking and draining of coasts) has been argued as a stop-gap measure to rising sea levels, but is it truly a long-lasting solution? 
 Capitalism. On a bigger picture, we have to evaluate capitalisms negative implications on climate change and global warming and think about the post-capitalist model.

This project reimagines a future of living on water whereby infrastructure and life is centred around a renewable material known as biorock, and natural sedimentation replaces the unsustainable practice of land reclamation. The methodology is derived from Landscape Urbanism and Form Axioms, using strategies such as Indexing, Prototyping and Meshing. The utilisation of the Ocean as the site provides a tebula rasa, in which design is not heavily pegged on any particular societal context or human bureaucracy. This leeway provides the possibilities of fictions to be generated, to envision man-made techno-derived society, and also to construct architecture not as a static realm, but as a series of ongoing phases.</description_of_project>
		<synopsis_of_project>This project reimagines a future of living on water whereby infrastructure and life is centred around a renewable material known as biorock, and natural sedimentation replaces the unsustainable practice of land reclamation.</synopsis_of_project>
		<keywords_of_project>climate, pondering, capitalism</keywords_of_project>
		<duration_of_solution>long</duration_of_solution>
		<primary_SDG>Climate Action</primary_SDG>
		<secondary_SDG>             Climate Action,    </secondary_SDG>
		<country_of_contribution>Singapore</country_of_contribution>
		<city_of_contribution>singapore</city_of_contribution>
		<lat>-8.754795</lat>
		<long>113.191252</long>
		<climate_hazard>climatological</climate_hazard>
		<project_ID>233620276</project_ID>
		<no_of_images>3</no_of_images>
		<category_of_contribution>solutions_to_adapt_to_climate_</category_of_contribution>
		<extra_links>https://www.asd.sutd.edu.sg/gradshow/march/projects/2020/wengshern-poon/</extra_links>
	</project>
	<project ID="233622069">
		<Name>Ooi</Name>
		<Surname>SooHao</Surname>
		<Affiliation>singapore_university_of_technology_and_d</Affiliation>
		<City_of_Institution>singapore</City_of_Institution>
		<country_001>Singapore</country_001>
		<title_of_project>Chargroforestry: The Carbon-sequestering  regenerative Agricultural Landscape</title_of_project>
		<credits_for_project>Ooi SooHao</credits_for_project>
		<year_of_project>2022</year_of_project>
		<description_of_project>The thesis - Chargroforestry aims to reimagine the urban landscape in the land-scarce Garden City by integrating various green plots with the industrial, commercial and community typology. While creating a circular agricultural production, the intervention also maximises the carbon sequestration through the renewable biomass from the agricultural production and the horticultural activity around the city. By not interfering the harmony of the urban fabric, Chargroforestry lies low to provide the community a lush and serene environment along their daily commutes and progressively towards a circular ecology and carbon-neutral lifestyle.</description_of_project>
		<synopsis_of_project>Chargroforestry aims to reimagine the urban landscape in the land-scarce Garden City by integrating various green plots with the industrial, commercial and community typology.</synopsis_of_project>
		<keywords_of_project>climate, garden city, Chargroforestry</keywords_of_project>
		<duration_of_solution>long</duration_of_solution>
		<primary_SDG>Climate Action</primary_SDG>
		<secondary_SDG>         Industry, Innovation and Infrastructure,    Climate Action,    </secondary_SDG>
		<country_of_contribution>Singapore</country_of_contribution>
		<city_of_contribution>singapore</city_of_contribution>
		<lat>-7.362467</lat>
		<long>119.523335</long>
		<climate_hazard>geophysical</climate_hazard>
		<project_ID>233622069</project_ID>
		<no_of_images>3</no_of_images>
		<category_of_contribution>solutions_to_adapt_to_climate_</category_of_contribution>
		<extra_links>https://asd.sutd.edu.sg/gradshow/march/projects/2022/soohao-ooi/</extra_links>
	</project>
	<project ID="233622535">
		<Name>Ng Wen</Name>
		<Surname>Qi</Surname>
		<Affiliation>singapore_university_of_technology_and_d</Affiliation>
		<City_of_Institution>singapore</City_of_Institution>
		<country_001>Singapore</country_001>
		<title_of_project>Rebuilding Paradise: wildfire architecture  designing for adaptive resilience</title_of_project>
		<credits_for_project>Ng Wen Qi</credits_for_project>
		<year_of_project>2021</year_of_project>
		<description_of_project>As urban habitats and natural landscapes become increasingly intermixed, wildfires that are capable of devastating entire towns and communities have become commonplace in wildland-urban interface areas. This thesis takes a critical relook at wildfire resilience by understanding the wildfire crisis in the Californian context, where the pursuit towards aggressively fortifying urban habitats has become modus operandi. In proposing the alternative premise of wildfire inevitability and reframing the idea of resilience towards one that designs for wildfire-adapted rather than wildfire-resistant communities, this project takes reference to resilient wildfire ecosystems as its architectural design framework. 

Ultimately, the vision for Rebuilding Paradise brings forward an alternative way of approaching wildfire resilience from an ecological perspective that allows suburban communities and their surrounding ecological systems to coexist synchronously with one another. It is a rebuttal against the typically loss-adverse, hyper-defensive narrative for resilience, proposing instead for an approach of targeted loss and regeneration.</description_of_project>
		<synopsis_of_project>The vision for Rebuilding Paradise brings forward an alternative way of approaching wildfire resilience from an ecological perspective that allows suburban communities and their surrounding ecological systems to coexist synchronously with one another.</synopsis_of_project>
		<keywords_of_project>wildfire, resilience</keywords_of_project>
		<duration_of_solution>long</duration_of_solution>
		<primary_SDG>Climate Action</primary_SDG>
		<secondary_SDG>             Climate Action,    </secondary_SDG>
		<country_of_contribution>Singapore</country_of_contribution>
		<city_of_contribution>california</city_of_contribution>
		<lat>1.757537</lat>
		<long>-113.35659</long>
		<climate_hazard>climatological</climate_hazard>
		<project_ID>233622535</project_ID>
		<no_of_images>3</no_of_images>
		<category_of_contribution>solutions_to_adapt_to_climate_</category_of_contribution>
		<extra_links>https://www.asd.sutd.edu.sg/gradshow/march/projects/2020/wenqi-ng/</extra_links>
	</project>
	<project ID="233702323">
		<Name>YUQIN</Name>
		<Surname>ZHONG</Surname>
		<Affiliation>other</Affiliation>
		<City_of_Institution>Singapore</City_of_Institution>
		<country_001>Singapore</country_001>
		<title_of_project>Video of climate change observation</title_of_project>
		<credits_for_project>Zhong Yuqin</credits_for_project>
		<year_of_project>2023</year_of_project>
		<description_of_project>An observation video on traits of climate change in daily life</description_of_project>
		<synopsis_of_project>Bring attention to general public on global warming</synopsis_of_project>
		<keywords_of_project>NA</keywords_of_project>
		<duration_of_solution>long</duration_of_solution>
		<primary_SDG>Climate Action</primary_SDG>
		<secondary_SDG>
		</secondary_SDG>
		<country_of_contribution>Singapore</country_of_contribution>
		<city_of_contribution>SINGAPORE</city_of_contribution>
		<lat>1.296207</lat>
		<long>103.864404</long>
		<climate_hazard>meteorological</climate_hazard>
		<project_ID>233702323</project_ID>
		<no_of_images>1</no_of_images>
		<category_of_contribution>narrative_of_climate_change___</category_of_contribution>
		<extra_links>NA</extra_links>
	</project>
	<project ID="233762889">
		<Name>Jannik</Name>
		<Surname>Ehlers</Surname>
		<Affiliation>rwth_aachen__germany</Affiliation>
		<City_of_Institution>Aachen</City_of_Institution>
		<country_001>Germany</country_001>
		<title_of_project>Reisholzer Hafen - Urban.Wandelbar.Schaffend</title_of_project>
		<credits_for_project>Ehlers, Jannik RWTH Aachen</credits_for_project>
		<year_of_project>2023</year_of_project>
		<description_of_project>In the next few years, the city of Dusseldorf would like to develop the old Reisholz harbour into a trimodal container harbour to supply the surrounding industrial and commercial areas. But how can such an extensive investment be used in the future and adapted to new requirements, even after the decline in logistics volumes? The key here, just as in logistics, lies in the standardisation of space modules that, flexibly interconnected, make new buildings possible and make them changeable, thus creating a new kind of city.</description_of_project>
		<synopsis_of_project>Any new development should be transformable and evolvable</synopsis_of_project>
		<keywords_of_project>transformable, evolvable, future, large project, modular</keywords_of_project>
		<duration_of_solution>long</duration_of_solution>
		<primary_SDG>Sustainable Cities and Communities</primary_SDG>
		<secondary_SDG>         Industry, Innovation and Infrastructure,        </secondary_SDG>
		<country_of_contribution>Germany</country_of_contribution>
		<city_of_contribution>Dusseldorf</city_of_contribution>
		<lat>51.159939</lat>
		<long>6.829041</long>
		<climate_hazard>Hydrological</climate_hazard>
		<project_ID>233762889</project_ID>
		<no_of_images>3</no_of_images>
		<category_of_contribution>solutions_to_adapt_to_climate_</category_of_contribution>
		<extra_links>NA</extra_links>
	</project>
	<project ID="233986066">
		<Name>Nibal</Name>
		<Surname>Hameed</Surname>
		<Affiliation>other</Affiliation>
		<City_of_Institution>Amman</City_of_Institution>
		<country_001>Jordan</country_001>
		<title_of_project>Role of Green infrastructure in Climate Adaptation: The Case of Quraish Street.</title_of_project>
		<credits_for_project>Thesis Student: Nibal Hameed Thesis Supervisor: Dr. Farah al Atrash</credits_for_project>
		<year_of_project>2022</year_of_project>
		<description_of_project>In line with the climate challenges Amman is facing, innovative solutions should be implemented to uphold various effects and increase the citys adaptive capacity. Many researchers proposed green infrastructure as a means for climate adaptation in Amman downtown. However, little effort was made to quantify the effects of these solutions. In order to identify the role of Green Infrastructure in climate adaptation, Quraish Street in Amman is chosen as a case study to represent a dense urban environment that has a high share of impermeable reflective surfaces and lacks proper vegetation. The research employed a dynamic simulation strategy using computational simulations to quantify the effects of different green infrastructure scenarios on heat mitigation, air pollutants reduction, and stormwater management. The scenario-based approach was used enabling community and expert participation along with site assessment and analysis in the design phase. Results indicate that using planters with dense trees has notable effects on heat mitigation but negligible effects on pollutant concentrations. In contrast, sparse tree canopies showed negligible effects on heat mitigation and also negligible effects on pollutant concentrations. The use of stormwater planters for runoff management showed minimal effects on runoff reductions. In contrast, the green envelope scenario showed notable effects on stormwater runoff reductions and negligible effects on heat mitigations and pollutants concentrations.</description_of_project>
		<synopsis_of_project>Integrating nature based solutions into urban environment can have great influence in the field of climate action</synopsis_of_project>
		<keywords_of_project>Green Infrastructure, Climate Adaptation, Urban Greening, SDG11, Urban Resilience</keywords_of_project>
		<duration_of_solution>long</duration_of_solution>
		<primary_SDG>Sustainable Cities and Communities</primary_SDG>
		<secondary_SDG>             Climate Action,    </secondary_SDG>
		<country_of_contribution>Jordan</country_of_contribution>
		<city_of_contribution>Amman</city_of_contribution>
		<lat>31.947625</lat>
		<long>35.934511</long>
		<climate_hazard>meteorological</climate_hazard>
		<project_ID>233986066</project_ID>
		<no_of_images>3</no_of_images>
		<category_of_contribution>solutions_to_adapt_to_climate_</category_of_contribution>
		<extra_links>NA</extra_links>
	</project>
	<project ID="234206734">
		<Name>ISLAM</Name>
		<Surname>IDRIS</Surname>
		<Affiliation>politecnico_di_milano__italy</Affiliation>
		<City_of_Institution>PIACENZA</City_of_Institution>
		<country_001>Italy</country_001>
		<title_of_project>FINSTOWN SELF-SUFFICIENT COMMUNITY</title_of_project>
		<credits_for_project>Islam Idris</credits_for_project>
		<year_of_project>2022</year_of_project>
		<description_of_project>According to data from the National Farmers Union,  the UK is only self-sufficient in growing fruit 18  and only 55 in growing fresh vegetables for national consumption.
When the UK left the European Union, importing and exporting costs radically increased and certain products became unavailable depending on what trade deals they are able to accomplish. This created the possibility of the  United Kingdom not being able to supply everything that is needed.
This means that the rest of the diet is imported from around the world, which is resulting in many people exploring the alternative of being self-sufficient at home.
This thought became more popular due to the sudden awakening to climate change around the world as a response to the global pandemic.
Methods that encourage or aid self-sustainability are permaculture, sustainable agriculture (on a small or large scale), renewable energy, and autonomous building.

 Orkney is a member of the Northern Isles off the northern  coast of Scotland. Finstown is a settlement situated on the  Mainland, Orkney. It is a fertile place which already priorities  animal husbandry and agriculture. It has a small population  and currently acts as a commuter town as most inhabitants of  working age are employed in Stromness or Kirkwall. As a result,  there is very little economical or cultural activity.

the project aims to reimagine Finstown as a thriving, self-  suffcient community which uses the concept.
the thesis  will develop the  master plan, which will represent the growth of the new  development over the course of 40 years which will be a great oppertunity for orkney to supply the uk with the needs of the food in future.

the project interventions consider housing, business and  employment, culture, gardens, biodiversity and ecological  regeneration. This master plan will create the physical and  philosophical context for an individual projects which will  address these thematic areas while also integrating housing.</description_of_project>
		<synopsis_of_project>Building a sustainable, low carbon settlement. Reducing  large scale imports of construction materials by using  materials sourced from Orkney as much as possible. Energy is generated by ground source heat pumps,  wind turbines and existing tidal power systems. Access  to public foot paths, cycle ways and bus routes reduce  the need for residents to buy cars.</synopsis_of_project>
		<keywords_of_project>urban growth. landscape regeneration. self-sufficient community.urban development.building design. community interaction.agriculture.food production.soft mobility.connectivity.</keywords_of_project>
		<duration_of_solution>permanent</duration_of_solution>
		<primary_SDG>Sustainable Cities and Communities</primary_SDG>
		<secondary_SDG>               Life on Land,  </secondary_SDG>
		<country_of_contribution>United_Kingdom</country_of_contribution>
		<city_of_contribution>ORKENY</city_of_contribution>
		<lat>59.007253</lat>
		<long>-3.115849</long>
		<climate_hazard>meteorological Hydrological</climate_hazard>
		<project_ID>234206734</project_ID>
		<no_of_images>3</no_of_images>
		<category_of_contribution>solutions_to_adapt_to_climate_</category_of_contribution>
		<extra_links>NA</extra_links>
	</project>
	<project ID="234241035">
		<Name>Eder</Name>
		<Surname>de Oliveira Daniel</Surname>
		<Affiliation>other</Affiliation>
		<City_of_Institution>Sao Paulo</City_of_Institution>
		<country_001>Brazil</country_001>
		<title_of_project>Eco Parque Escola</title_of_project>
		<credits_for_project>Eder de Oliveira Daniel, coordinator EMEF Philo;  Claudinei Mendes da Silva, professor EMEF Philo;  Giseli de Oliveira Cardoso, professor EMEF Philo; Ana Cecilia Mattei de Arruda Campos, professor FAUUSP;  Euler Sandeville Junior, professor FAUUSP; Beatriz Neves Marques, graduate student FAUUSP; Isabela de Oliveira Dias, graduate student FAUUSP; Joao Francisco Spegiorin, graduate student FAUUSP; Stephanie Mark Li, graduate student FAUUSP.</credits_for_project>
		<year_of_project>2023</year_of_project>
		<description_of_project>The Eco Parque Escola project is the result of a community effort to change a landfill into a pedagogical open space. The public school named Philo Goncalves dos Santos, professors and students, together with professors and students of the School of Architecture and Urbanism of University of Sao Paulo (FAUUSP) and the team of Municipal Secretary of Environment of Sao Paulo City (SVMA) get together to create the park. Although the project is not implemented yet, the community is using the space informally, building by themselves trails, furniture, planting woods and other facilities to appropriate the space.</description_of_project>
		<synopsis_of_project>Eco Parque Escola: a way of teaching to protect the environment</synopsis_of_project>
		<keywords_of_project>environment,  sustainability,  Goals (SDG), environmental justice, participatory design</keywords_of_project>
		<duration_of_solution>permanent</duration_of_solution>
		<primary_SDG>Climate Action</primary_SDG>
		<secondary_SDG>   Good Health and Well-being,        Sustainable Cities and Communities,    Life on Land,  </secondary_SDG>
		<country_of_contribution>Brazil</country_of_contribution>
		<city_of_contribution>Sao Paulo</city_of_contribution>
		<lat>-23.401604</lat>
		<long>-46.74346</long>
		<climate_hazard>climatological</climate_hazard>
		<project_ID>234241035</project_ID>
		<no_of_images>3</no_of_images>
		<category_of_contribution>solutions_to_adapt_to_climate_</category_of_contribution>
		<extra_links>https://www.educacao.sme.prefeitura.sp.gov.br/noticias/emef-philo-desenvolve-projeto-de-eco-praca-em-parceria-com-faculdade-de-arquitetura-da-usp/ </extra_links>
	</project>
	<project ID="234584754">
		<Name>UIA</Name>
		<Surname>International Union of Architects</Surname>
		<Affiliation>other</Affiliation>
		<City_of_Institution>Paris</City_of_Institution>
		<country_001>France</country_001>
		<title_of_project> Dandelion ARC Journey</title_of_project>
		<credits_for_project>Yuto Takenaka from the Graduate School of Design, Harvard University, USA for the project Dandelion ARC Journey.</credits_for_project>
		<year_of_project>2022</year_of_project>
		<description_of_project>The International Union of Architects (UIA) launched the single stage international ideas competition for the Great Green Wall (GGW), open to architecture students from around the World. The objective of the competition was to spotlight innovative design ideas for providing simplified affordable housing within the 8000 km long and 16 km wide living region stretching across the Sahel-Savanah desert region, from Dakar to Djibouti, known as the Great Green Wall (GGW). The Dandelion presents a compelling proposal that actually frames the entire African Great Green Wall as a site. Its fantastic narrative explores the possibility of being both general and specific, contextual and
generic.</description_of_project>
		<synopsis_of_project>By reestablishing the interconnectivity of African peoples and inspiring ecological innovation, their community will grow strong like a Dandelion, growing a resilient Great Green Wall.</synopsis_of_project>
		<keywords_of_project>Architecture, Great Green Wall, Africa, Climate Change, Housing</keywords_of_project>
		<duration_of_solution>permanent</duration_of_solution>
		<primary_SDG>Sustainable Cities and Communities</primary_SDG>
		<secondary_SDG> No Poverty,  Good Health and Well-being,       Reduced Inequality,       </secondary_SDG>
		<country_of_contribution>Burkina</country_of_contribution>
		<city_of_contribution>Saouga</city_of_contribution>
		<lat>14.364931</lat>
		<long>-0.143104</long>
		<climate_hazard>climatological</climate_hazard>
		<project_ID>234584754</project_ID>
		<no_of_images>1</no_of_images>
		<category_of_contribution>solutions_to_adapt_to_climate_</category_of_contribution>
		<extra_links>https://www.uia-architectes.org/en/competition/great-green-wall-single-stage-student-ideas-competition/</extra_links>
	</project>
	<project ID="234586038">
		<Name>UIA</Name>
		<Surname>International Union of Architects</Surname>
		<Affiliation>other</Affiliation>
		<City_of_Institution>Paris</City_of_Institution>
		<country_001>France</country_001>
		<title_of_project> Sustainable housing for Africa</title_of_project>
		<credits_for_project>Altynai Isaeva from the Kyrgyz State University of Construction and
Architecture (KSUCTA), Kyrgyzstanfor the project Sustainable housing for Africa in Burkina Faso.
(First prize winner)</credits_for_project>
		<year_of_project>2022</year_of_project>
		<description_of_project>The International Union of Architects (UIA) launched the single stage
international ideas competition for the Great Green Wall (GGW), open to
architecture students from around the World. The objective of the
competition was to spotlight innovative design ideas for providing
simplified affordable housing within the 8000 km long and 16 km wide
living region stretching across the Sahel-Savanah desert region, from Dakar
to Djibouti, known as the Great Green Wall (GGW). The jury lauded the entry
for being a very mature and correct proposal, able to redeploy typological
memory and conceptual clarity through a simple configuration of a solid
base.</description_of_project>
		<synopsis_of_project>The project is aimed at providing the population with affordable housing in a hot, dry climate, taking into account the traditions of not one locality, not one country, but the unification of many peoples included in the line of the Great Green Wall.</synopsis_of_project>
		<keywords_of_project>Architecture, Great Green Wall, Africa, Climate Change, Housing</keywords_of_project>
		<duration_of_solution>permanent</duration_of_solution>
		<primary_SDG>Sustainable Cities and Communities</primary_SDG>
		<secondary_SDG> No Poverty,  Good Health and Well-being,       Reduced Inequality,       </secondary_SDG>
		<country_of_contribution>Burkina</country_of_contribution>
		<city_of_contribution>Saouga</city_of_contribution>
		<lat>14.364931</lat>
		<long>-0.143104</long>
		<climate_hazard>climatological</climate_hazard>
		<project_ID>234586038</project_ID>
		<no_of_images>1</no_of_images>
		<category_of_contribution>solutions_to_adapt_to_climate_</category_of_contribution>
		<extra_links>https://www.uia-architectes.org/en/competition/great-green-wall-singlestage-
student-ideas-competition/</extra_links>
	</project>
	<project ID="234587733">
		<Name>UIA</Name>
		<Surname>International Union of Architects</Surname>
		<Affiliation>other</Affiliation>
		<City_of_Institution>Paris</City_of_Institution>
		<country_001>France</country_001>
		<title_of_project>Green Colonies</title_of_project>
		<credits_for_project>Tian Haoran, Yang Mohan, Wu Ruopan and Cao Chuangwei supervised by tutors Hou Shuai and Ren Zhonglong from the Inner Mongolia University of Technology, China for the project Green Colonies in Niger.
Third Prize</credits_for_project>
		<year_of_project>2022</year_of_project>
		<description_of_project>The International Union of Architects (UIA) launched the single stage international ideas competition for the Great Green Wall (GGW), open to architecture students from around the World. The objective of the competition was to spotlight innovative design ideas for providing simplified affordable housing within the 8000 km long and 16 km wide living region stretching across the Sahel-Savanah desert region, from Dakar to Djibouti, known as the Great Green Wall (GGW). The Green Colonies project proposes a solution by transforming the courtyard house typology into an
organically growing habitat.</description_of_project>
		<synopsis_of_project>We propose that a new scheme that rearranges the relationship between people, vegetation, and constructions could be the answer. The core of this scheme is the courtyard, which would accommodate the vegetation that is protected and nurtured by man-made buildings. And further, the nurtured plants could make a better micro-climate and views for residents.</synopsis_of_project>
		<keywords_of_project>Architecture, Great Green Wall, Africa, Climate Change, Housing</keywords_of_project>
		<duration_of_solution>permanent</duration_of_solution>
		<primary_SDG>Sustainable Cities and Communities</primary_SDG>
		<secondary_SDG> No Poverty,  Good Health and Well-being,       Reduced Inequality,       </secondary_SDG>
		<country_of_contribution>Niger</country_of_contribution>
		<city_of_contribution>Zinder</city_of_contribution>
		<lat>13.806513</lat>
		<long>8.989174</long>
		<climate_hazard>climatological</climate_hazard>
		<project_ID>234587733</project_ID>
		<no_of_images>1</no_of_images>
		<category_of_contribution>solutions_to_adapt_to_climate_</category_of_contribution>
		<extra_links>https://www.uia-architectes.org/en/competition/great-green-wall-singlestage-student-ideas-competition/</extra_links>
	</project>
	<project ID="234589795">
		<Name>UIA</Name>
		<Surname>International Union of Architects</Surname>
		<Affiliation>other</Affiliation>
		<City_of_Institution>Paris</City_of_Institution>
		<country_001>France</country_001>
		<title_of_project>Co-Living</title_of_project>
		<credits_for_project>Quan Dao and Quang Ngo, Hanoi Architectural University, Vietnam for the project Co-Living in Burkina Faso.
4th prize</credits_for_project>
		<year_of_project>2022</year_of_project>
		<description_of_project>The International Union of Architects (UIA) launched the single stage international ideas competition for the Great Green Wall (GGW), open to architecture students from around the World. The objective of the competition was to spotlight innovative design ideas for providing simplified affordable housing within the 8000 km long and 16 km wide living region stretching across the Sahel-Savanah desert region, from Dakar to Djibouti, known as the Great Green Wall (GGW). The proposal was inspired by the traditional organic configuration that transformed into an organised geometric order. It offers an elegant tropical solution that reminded the jury of Francis Keres work and acts as a living obstacle to the Sahara progress.</description_of_project>
		<synopsis_of_project>This project aims to gather human resources for the task of developing sustainable agriculture around the accommodation area, saving water and utilizing sustainable material.</synopsis_of_project>
		<keywords_of_project>Architecture, Great Green Wall, Africa, Climate Change, Housing</keywords_of_project>
		<duration_of_solution>permanent</duration_of_solution>
		<primary_SDG>Sustainable Cities and Communities</primary_SDG>
		<secondary_SDG> No Poverty,  Good Health and Well-being,       Reduced Inequality,       </secondary_SDG>
		<country_of_contribution>Burkina</country_of_contribution>
		<city_of_contribution>Lattou</city_of_contribution>
		<lat>12.277067</lat>
		<long>-2.360004</long>
		<climate_hazard>climatological</climate_hazard>
		<project_ID>234589795</project_ID>
		<no_of_images>1</no_of_images>
		<category_of_contribution>solutions_to_adapt_to_climate_</category_of_contribution>
		<extra_links>https://www.uia-architectes.org/en/competition/great-green-wall-single-stage-student-ideas-competition/</extra_links>
	</project>
	<project ID="234591745">
		<Name>UIA</Name>
		<Surname>International Union of Architects</Surname>
		<Affiliation>other</Affiliation>
		<City_of_Institution>Paris</City_of_Institution>
		<country_001>France</country_001>
		<title_of_project>The Gidajen Laka</title_of_project>
		<credits_for_project>Abdulhameed Yakubu, Khadija Oyanki, Rayyan Garba and Amina Musa from Ahmadu Bello University, Nigeria for the project The Gidajen Laka in Nigeria.
5th prize</credits_for_project>
		<year_of_project>2022</year_of_project>
		<description_of_project>The International Union of Architects (UIA) launched the single stage international ideas competition for the Great Green Wall (GGW), open to architecture students from around the World. The objective of the competition was to spotlight innovative design ideas for providing simplified affordable housing within the 8000 km long and 16 km wide living region stretching across the Sahel-Savanah desert region, from Dakar to Djibouti, known as the Great Green Wall (GGW). The Gidajen Laka proposal for Northeastern Nigeria successfully incorporates a courtyard as a living space in a single-family dwelling. This typology is culturally rooted along the entire line of the Great Green Wall. Moreover, it is functional in the prevailing climate and saves material. Additionally, the proposal is
constructed of sustainable building materials, preserving the local know-how of utilizing adobe.</description_of_project>
		<synopsis_of_project>This design approach is aimed at engaging and empowering members of the community and promoting their participation in the developmental continuity of their community.</synopsis_of_project>
		<keywords_of_project>Architecture, Great Green Wall, Africa, Climate Change, Housing</keywords_of_project>
		<duration_of_solution>permanent</duration_of_solution>
		<primary_SDG>Sustainable Cities and Communities</primary_SDG>
		<secondary_SDG> No Poverty,  Good Health and Well-being,       Reduced Inequality,       </secondary_SDG>
		<country_of_contribution>Nigeria</country_of_contribution>
		<city_of_contribution>Sokoto State</city_of_contribution>
		<lat>13.591703</lat>
		<long>5.905876</long>
		<climate_hazard>climatological</climate_hazard>
		<project_ID>234591745</project_ID>
		<no_of_images>1</no_of_images>
		<category_of_contribution>solutions_to_adapt_to_climate_</category_of_contribution>
		<extra_links>https://www.uia-architectes.org/en/competition/great-green-wall-single-stage-student-ideas-competition/</extra_links>
	</project>
	<project ID="240278897">
		<Name>Plam</Name>
		<Surname>Creative Studio</Surname>
		<Affiliation>other</Affiliation>
		<City_of_Institution>Ferrara</City_of_Institution>
		<country_001>Italy</country_001>
		<title_of_project>Tuboo</title_of_project>
		<credits_for_project>Arianna Montinaro
Andrea Miljevic
Andrea Pradella
Luca Pradella</credits_for_project>
		<year_of_project>2023</year_of_project>
		<description_of_project>TuBOO is a project designed by Plam Creative Studio on the occasion of the temporary exhibition for Climate Wunderkammer, an open source collective archive.
Both typology of seats, made out of pvc water pipes, are designed on the inspiration of Japanese Bamboos bending traditional technique.
TuBoo is meant as a case history to be included in the Climate Wunderkammers archive: a design approach that opens a reflection, addressing the themes of "de-contextualize" and "re-interpret". How can the ancient technique meet the current technology and trigger re-thinking processes?
The seats are made out of orange pvc water pipes, normally used in the building field. The pipes are heated and folded in new shapes. The connection between modules is made through a standard steel tensioner.
TuBoo minimizes the type of materials used to respond to the function that the object must perform.
Thanks to the lightness and the resistance of pvc, the seats are easy to assemble, disassemble and transport; they can be quickly recomposed in the exhibition room and also can be used in outdoor space.</description_of_project>
		<synopsis_of_project>How can the ancient technique meet the current technology and trigger re-thinking processes?</synopsis_of_project>
		<keywords_of_project>RETHINKING, DECONTEXTUALIZED, REINTERPRET, PVC, BAMBOO</keywords_of_project>
		<duration_of_solution>Temporary (Short term)</duration_of_solution>
		<primary_SDG>Responsible Consumption and Production</primary_SDG>
		<secondary_SDG>           Sustainable Cities and Communities,      </secondary_SDG>
		<country_of_contribution>Italy</country_of_contribution>
		<city_of_contribution>FERRARA</city_of_contribution>
		<lat>44.831351</lat>
		<long>11.61941</long>
		<climate_hazard>Meteorological</climate_hazard>
		<project_ID>240278897</project_ID>
		<no_of_images>3</no_of_images>
		<category_of_contribution>Solutions to adapt to climate change; </category_of_contribution>
		<extra_links>https://www.plamstudio.eu/tuboo</extra_links>
	</project>
	<project ID="242185682">
		<Name>Yueqi</Name>
		<Surname>Zhang</Surname>
		<Affiliation>TU Delft, The Netherlands</Affiliation>
		<City_of_Institution>Delft</City_of_Institution>
		<country_001>Netherlands</country_001>
		<title_of_project>Through lake and swamp-An adaptive wetland production transformation</title_of_project>
		<credits_for_project>Yueqi Zhang,  Technische Universiteit Delft, Msc Architecture,Urbanism and Landscape Archtecture(track Urbaism)</credits_for_project>
		<year_of_project>2023</year_of_project>
		<description_of_project>This project focuses on the sustainable development of Anxin County, situated in the Xiongan New Area of China. The aim is to create a harmonious balance between economic growth and ecological preservation, considering the regions unique characteristics, such as the Baiyangdian wetland and the surrounding rural landscape. Taking the local wetland productive system as a starting point, the project explores the possibilities of the local agricultural landscape to be adapted to the rapid urbanization process as well as providing a climate-resilient solution for the hydrological crisis.

A strategic map has been formulated through a comprehensive analysis and evaluation of scenario building. This map emphasizes the integration of local industries, namely reed cultivation, fishery and other primary industries, and ecological preservation. By promoting the sustainability of the local industry, a more coordinated network will be built to provide enough job opportunities to residents and protect the ecological sensitivity of the wetland at the same time. The goal is to enhance the ecological and social resilience of the area and establish a sustainable development model that can be replicated in the North China Plain area.</description_of_project>
		<synopsis_of_project>Preservation and adaptation together pave the way for a resilient future amidst climate change.</synopsis_of_project>
		<keywords_of_project>Climate resilience, industrial transformation, agricultural landscape, regional planning, megaregion intergration, wetland ecology</keywords_of_project>
		<duration_of_solution>Long-term (decades)</duration_of_solution>
		<primary_SDG>Sustainable Cities and Communities</primary_SDG>
		<secondary_SDG>        Decent Work and Economic Growth, Industry, Innovation and Infrastructure,   Responsible Consumption and Production,     </secondary_SDG>
		<country_of_contribution>China</country_of_contribution>
		<city_of_contribution>Baoding</city_of_contribution>
		<lat>38.92981</lat>
		<long>115.927545</long>
		<climate_hazard>Climatological Geophysical</climate_hazard>
		<project_ID>242185682</project_ID>
		<no_of_images>3</no_of_images>
		<category_of_contribution>Solutions to adapt to climate change; </category_of_contribution>
		<extra_links>NA</extra_links>
	</project>
	<project ID="246296038">
		<Name>Giulia</Name>
		<Surname>Castellazzi</Surname>
		<Affiliation>other</Affiliation>
		<City_of_Institution>Milano</City_of_Institution>
		<country_001>Italy</country_001>
		<title_of_project>SLOPE INSTABILITIES DRIVEN BY GLACIER MELTING PROCESSES: a GIS-based approach for Landslide Risk Assessment in the Alpine landscapes of Valle dAosta</title_of_project>
		<credits_for_project>Giulia Castellazzi, Author
Mattia Previtali, Supervisor (Politecnico di Milano)</credits_for_project>
		<year_of_project>2021</year_of_project>
		<description_of_project>The identification of dangerous areas is crucial for developing environmental risk reduction strategies. While various methods exist for assessing and computing individual sub-components, there is a lack of applying the entire risk assessment procedure over large areas to directly inform the design of regional and municipal risk mitigation policies. This research focuses on landslides and gravitational movements resulting from rapid glacier melting in the Valle dAosta region in Italy, with the aim of providing a tool that can support spatial planning in response to climate change in Alpine environments, landscapes that can be extremely fragile, but also very dangerous at the same time. By employing a GIS-based and multi-scalar approach, the study estimated the risk by defining hazard indexes that consider various aspects. It draws upon knowledge from diverse disciplinary fields and establishes an initial regional framework. The assessment was then deepened for the Lys River Valley, where hazardous areas were mapped, and buildings were classified based on their hazard scores. Furthermore, the study selected four survey areas representing different landscape typologies in Valle dAosta where a detailed vulnerability analysis was conducted, resulting in an estimation of potential damage and overall risk associated with slope instability events at the local scale.</description_of_project>
		<synopsis_of_project>Alpine landscapes possess a delicate nature, characterized by both fragility and inherent danger: the identification of hazard areas is a crucial step to develop environmental risk reduction strategies, increasing the resilience of our territories.</synopsis_of_project>
		<keywords_of_project>Alpine Landscape, Slope Instability, Glacier Melting, Risk Assessment, GIS methodology</keywords_of_project>
		<duration_of_solution>Long-term (decades)</duration_of_solution>
		<primary_SDG>Climate Action</primary_SDG>
		<secondary_SDG>   Good Health and Well-being,        Sustainable Cities and Communities,      Partnerships to achieve the Goal,</secondary_SDG>
		<country_of_contribution>Italy</country_of_contribution>
		<city_of_contribution>Valle dAosta</city_of_contribution>
		<lat>45.828159</lat>
		<long>7.824986</long>
		<climate_hazard>Geophysical</climate_hazard>
		<project_ID>246296038</project_ID>
		<no_of_images>3</no_of_images>
		<category_of_contribution>Narrative of climate change - observing and reporting the impact of a changing climate</category_of_contribution>
		<extra_links>NA</extra_links>
	</project>
	<project ID="248209098">
		<Name>Malena</Name>
		<Surname>Bertotti</Surname>
		<Affiliation>Politecnico Di Milano, Italy</Affiliation>
		<City_of_Institution>Piacenza</City_of_Institution>
		<country_001>Italy</country_001>
		<title_of_project>The butterfly effect</title_of_project>
		<credits_for_project>Bertotti, Malena - Politecnico di Milano 
Dong, Wenjing - Politecnico di Milano
Lahor, Elif - Politecnico di Milano 
Rodriguez, Sandra - Politecnico di Milano 
Valarezo, Isabella - Politecnico di Milano 
Zauron, Maryam - Politecnico di Milano</credits_for_project>
		<year_of_project>2023</year_of_project>
		<description_of_project>In chaos theory, the butterfly effect is the sensitive dependence on initial conditions in which a small change in one state of a deterministic nonlinear system can result in large differences in a later state. The butterfly effect main goal is to regenerate the urban environment with a "low profile" approach, with a particular focus on restoring ecosystem quality and the connection between urbanity and nature. Not only from the perspective of humans, also considering the wildlife as main characters of this project. In addition to the interventions themselves, we aim to promote a culture of care and respect for nature among the urban community. We envision a city where environmental health is a top priority and all inhabitants can enjoy a healthier, safer environment that positively impacts their quality of life and well-being.</description_of_project>
		<synopsis_of_project>It is never to late to start appreciating and protecting our nature resources.</synopsis_of_project>
		<keywords_of_project>observatory, environmental, climate change, biodiversity</keywords_of_project>
		<duration_of_solution>Long-term (decades)</duration_of_solution>
		<primary_SDG>Sustainable Cities and Communities</primary_SDG>
		<secondary_SDG>       Clean Water and Sanitation,           </secondary_SDG>
		<country_of_contribution>Spain</country_of_contribution>
		<city_of_contribution>Barcelona</city_of_contribution>
		<lat>41.351169</lat>
		<long>2.093889</long>
		<climate_hazard>Climatological Hydrological</climate_hazard>
		<project_ID>248209098</project_ID>
		<no_of_images>3</no_of_images>
		<category_of_contribution>Solutions to adapt to climate change; </category_of_contribution>
		<extra_links>NA</extra_links>
	</project>
	<project ID="249905015">
		<Name>Lux</Name>
		<Surname>Meteora</Surname>
		<Affiliation>other</Affiliation>
		<City_of_Institution>Madrid</City_of_Institution>
		<country_001>Spain</country_001>
		<title_of_project>A FIERY EXCHANGE</title_of_project>
		<credits_for_project>Lux Meteora</credits_for_project>
		<year_of_project>2023</year_of_project>
		<description_of_project>Fire is destructive, yet it can be regenerative as well. A Fiery Exchange is a NbS webcomic that tackles the problematic surrounding fire and fire policies.</description_of_project>
		<synopsis_of_project>What if fire were used for good instead of just being seen as a destructive force of nature?</synopsis_of_project>
		<keywords_of_project>Wildfire, prescribed fire, preventive fire, fire policy, fire suppression</keywords_of_project>
		<duration_of_solution>Long-term (decades) Permanent (centuries)</duration_of_solution>
		<primary_SDG>Climate Action</primary_SDG>
		<secondary_SDG> No Poverty,  Good Health and Well-being,            Life on Land,  </secondary_SDG>
		<country_of_contribution>Spain</country_of_contribution>
		<city_of_contribution>Sierra de la Culebra</city_of_contribution>
		<lat>41.905664</lat>
		<long>-6.330467</long>
		<climate_hazard>Meteorological Climatological Biological</climate_hazard>
		<project_ID>249905015</project_ID>
		<no_of_images>3</no_of_images>
		<category_of_contribution>Narrative of climate change - observing and reporting the impact of a changing climate</category_of_contribution>
		<extra_links>https://www.nbscomics.com/202306072023-a-fiery-exchange</extra_links>
	</project>
	<project ID="258366973">
		<Name>Nabil</Name>
		<Surname>Mohareb</Surname>
		<Affiliation>other</Affiliation>
		<City_of_Institution>Cairo</City_of_Institution>
		<country_001>Egypt</country_001>
		<title_of_project>Reuse of ancient towers</title_of_project>
		<credits_for_project>Mariam Maged, Future University</credits_for_project>
		<year_of_project>2023</year_of_project>
		<description_of_project>This project introduces a visionary approach to revitalizing Southern Italian coastal watchtowers, amalgamating historical restoration with contemporary functionality. The strategy encompasses two pivotal facets: "Collective Revival" and "Individual Performance."

The "Collective Revival" entails a captivating seasonal contest uniting the watchtowers via a dynamic treasure hunt trail, emanating from distinct towers and imparting historical narratives. This immersive journey not only highlights each towers uniqueness but also forges a cohesive coastal identity as participants traverse sea and shore routes. Reestablishing visual and physical communication channels connecting participating towers.

Simultaneously, the "Individual Performance" aspect focuses on enhancing the distinctive attributes of each tower. Elements encompass designated shaded seating, elevated platforms for panoramic views, projection screens for nocturnal activities, and cafe facilities. Exemplified by the Torre Rinalda case, an innovative wooden ramp enriches both accessibility and aesthetics.

The design maintains historical integrity through steel frames outlining original silhouettes, complete with light and smoke pipes that echo historical functionality. Utilizing sustainable materials like naturally recycled wood underscores the eco-conscious approach. Interactive shading devices (wings) provide adaptable configurations for diverse weather and activities.

This visionary concept rejuvenates watchtowers, harmonizing history, innovation, and sustainability along the Southern Italian coast, forging a resilient and vibrant coastal community.</description_of_project>
		<synopsis_of_project>Revitalizing disused heritage structures offers a sustainable path forward amidst the pressing climate crisis.</synopsis_of_project>
		<keywords_of_project>Italian watching towers, reuse of old buildings, reuse towers</keywords_of_project>
		<duration_of_solution>Temporary (Short term)</duration_of_solution>
		<primary_SDG>Sustainable Cities and Communities</primary_SDG>
		<secondary_SDG>                 Partnerships to achieve the Goal,</secondary_SDG>
		<country_of_contribution>Italy</country_of_contribution>
		<city_of_contribution>Lecce</city_of_contribution>
		<lat>40.396599</lat>
		<long>18.292891</long>
		<climate_hazard>Hydrological Geophysical</climate_hazard>
		<project_ID>258366973</project_ID>
		<no_of_images>3</no_of_images>
		<category_of_contribution>Solutions to adapt to climate change; </category_of_contribution>
		<extra_links>NA</extra_links>
	</project>
</data-set>
