<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<data-set>
	<project ID="230526388">
		<Name>Ricardo</Name>
		<Surname>da Cruz e Sousa</Surname>
		<Affiliation>other</Affiliation>
		<City_of_Institution>Rio de Janeiro</City_of_Institution>
		<country_001>Brazil</country_001>
		<title_of_project>Climate Risks and Adaptation Solutions in Copacabana</title_of_project>
		<credits_for_project>Ricardo da Cruz e Sousa, Universidade Federal do Rio de Janeiro</credits_for_project>
		<year_of_project>2022</year_of_project>
		<description_of_project>This video is intended to be used as a communication tool on climate change to increase public awareness and perception of adaptation risks and solutions in Copacabana in Rio de Janeiro. Copacabana has the densest coastal urbanization in Brazil, which, combined with an aging and inefficient infrastructure, increases the populations exposure and vulnerability to climate risks. Through visual representation and a narrative, this approach to landscape design generates new knowledge and communicates it visually to elicit emotional responses, interest, debate, behavioral change and climate action.</description_of_project>
		<synopsis_of_project>This video aims to increase public awareness and perception of climate change risks and solutions in Copacabana, Brazil, through visual representation and narrative.</synopsis_of_project>
		<keywords_of_project>Adaptation, climate change, copacabana, landscape, risks.</keywords_of_project>
		<duration_of_solution>long</duration_of_solution>
		<primary_SDG>Climate Action</primary_SDG>
		<secondary_SDG>          Reduced Inequality, Sustainable Cities and Communities,   Life Below Water,   </secondary_SDG>
		<country_of_contribution>Brazil</country_of_contribution>
		<city_of_contribution>Rio de Janeiro</city_of_contribution>
		<lat>-22.969759</lat>
		<long>-43.186379</long>
		<climate_hazard>meteorological climatological Hydrological geophysical</climate_hazard>
		<project_ID>230526388</project_ID>
	</project>
	<project ID="230585066">
		<Name>Sina</Name>
		<Surname>Hensel</Surname>
		<Affiliation>rwth_aachen__germany</Affiliation>
		<City_of_Institution>Aachen</City_of_Institution>
		<country_001>Germany</country_001>
		<title_of_project>SUNBURN</title_of_project>
		<credits_for_project>Sina Hensel, director, cinematography, editing
(Sina Hensel is a visual artist and researcher based in Brussels)
Rosa Whiteley, director, cinematography, editing
(Rosa Whiteley is an architectural researcher based in London)
Simonluca Laitempergher, sound production
PACT Zollverein, production</credits_for_project>
		<year_of_project>2021</year_of_project>
		<description_of_project>Sunscreens are no longer just applied to our skins, but also to the skins of mountains, clouds, or trees. As we struggle to control shifting climates and our ability to adapt to them, sunscreening has grown in size, through solar geoengineering, to encompass the planet. Skins in different bodies - cells, species, ecologies, territories and technologies - often change colour in a reaction to UV light. Chemical alarms in cells trigger inflammation and metabolic mechanisms produce protective pigments. Leaves flash red, algae secrete pink, whilst humans smear shades of white. As climate related stress amplifies, colours strain to perform resistance. These colours act as both a defence and a signal for the intensity of the sun; bearing the impressions of the weather-world. SUNBURN explores the spaces between colourful feral ecologies, and synthetic post-human skins; uncovering methods of living in a hotter, sun- scorched earth. Whilst sunscreening occurs differently in different species, from whales to trees, this film explores four methods and acts of sunscreening; Spraying, Secreteing, Smearing or Costuming.</description_of_project>
		<synopsis_of_project>Sunscreening has grown in size due to solar geoengineering, and skins in different bodies change colour in response to UV light. This film explores four methods of sunscreening: spraying, secreteing, smearing or costuming. It explores the spaces between feral ecologies and synthetic post-human skins.</synopsis_of_project>
		<keywords_of_project>UV-Radiation, (Skin)Care, Sunscreen, Shifting Climate, Sun</keywords_of_project>
		<duration_of_solution>long</duration_of_solution>
		<primary_SDG>Life on Land</primary_SDG>
		<secondary_SDG>             Climate Action,    </secondary_SDG>
		<country_of_contribution>Germany</country_of_contribution>
		<city_of_contribution>Aachen</city_of_contribution>
		<lat>50.778216</lat>
		<long>6.07825</long>
		<climate_hazard>meteorological biological</climate_hazard>
		<project_ID>230585066</project_ID>
	</project>
	<project ID="230866616">
		<Name>Raquel</Name>
		<Surname>Domingues</Surname>
		<Affiliation>Chalmers</Affiliation>
		<City_of_Institution>Gothenburg</City_of_Institution>
		<country_001>Sweden</country_001>
		<title_of_project>Acrodystopia</title_of_project>
		<credits_for_project>Ellen Boman, Chalmers University of Technology
Li Wallin, Chalmers University of Technology
Nelson Mouketa, Chalmers University of Technology
Raquel Domingues, Chalmers University of Technology</credits_for_project>
		<year_of_project>2021</year_of_project>
		<description_of_project>In this futuristic dystopian scenario where cities are flooded and civilisation as we know it has changed forever, people turn to innovation to survive.

Isolated on one of the citys last standing bridges, a group of people have developed the abandoned space into a secure settlement. Many years have passed since the uprising and a new society has risen from the rubble. The sea level is still high and most of the city is inaccessible without water travel. The ebb and flow have also reached new extremes, and the bridge floods when the tide is high.

The spherical pods are designed to roll and move on land, float and move on water, and connect with other pods to form a whole intricate system. The idea behind the adaptable approach is to make pods resilient to future emergencies. With them being so mobile, people are not as exposed to the new challenges they might face. Inspired by biomimicry, the outer shell rotates and steers the pod and can open up and let in light. Between the outer and inner shells is a layer of ball-bearing and hot air from the stove. Hot air insulation keeps the surrounding water from freezing.</description_of_project>
		<synopsis_of_project>We can create a new way of living by building a community-based society with adaptable housing and transportation pods, coping with water floods and scarcity, utilizing local resources, and incorporating innovations.</synopsis_of_project>
		<keywords_of_project>Adaptability, Resilience, Circularity, Community, Eco-Machines</keywords_of_project>
		<duration_of_solution>long</duration_of_solution>
		<primary_SDG>Sustainable Cities and Communities</primary_SDG>
		<secondary_SDG>             Climate Action,    </secondary_SDG>
		<country_of_contribution>Sweden</country_of_contribution>
		<city_of_contribution>Gothenburg</city_of_contribution>
		<lat>57.703991</lat>
		<long>11.962271</long>
		<climate_hazard>Hydrological</climate_hazard>
		<project_ID>230866616</project_ID>
	</project>
	<project ID="230939140">
		<Name>ana cecilia</Name>
		<Surname>campos</Surname>
		<Affiliation>other</Affiliation>
		<City_of_Institution>Sao Paulo</City_of_Institution>
		<country_001>Brazil</country_001>
		<title_of_project>Eco Park Philo - a community challenge</title_of_project>
		<credits_for_project>Ana Cecilia Campos, professor at FAUUSP, School of Architecture, Urbanism and Design of University of Sao Paulo</credits_for_project>
		<year_of_project>2023</year_of_project>
		<description_of_project>I am Ana Cecilia Campos, architect, from Sao Paulo, Brazil. As a professor at the School of Architecture, Urbanism and Design of University of Sao Paulo, with professor Euler Sandeville, we received in 2021 a call from a public school - Philo Goncalves dos Santos, in Perus, a peripheral neighborhood, to convert an open space, with no qualifications, into an eco-park. It was a very special request - the area was thought as a pedagogical space, where students and teachers could study through the park, living the open space. 

In a participatory process, we developed the project with our students together with teachers, students, parents, and employees from the Philo School. We are still together in 2023 trying to implement the park. Although, the school is already using the space for educational activities and events, an appropriation of the place.

We also brought public managers to fulfill the dialogue - the park is close to the ecological corridors of Sao Paulo City. The Environmental Municipal Secretary will start educational programs on urban gardens. 

According to an urban planning process based on horizontal dialogue, school, community, public managers and university are working for this common environmental objective. The process changed us all!</description_of_project>
		<synopsis_of_project>Think and create a better environment for all</synopsis_of_project>
		<keywords_of_project>eco-park, participatory design, community challenge, open spaces, pedagogical space</keywords_of_project>
		<duration_of_solution>long</duration_of_solution>
		<primary_SDG>Sustainable Cities and Communities</primary_SDG>
		<secondary_SDG>                 Partnerships to achieve the Goal,</secondary_SDG>
		<country_of_contribution>Brazil</country_of_contribution>
		<city_of_contribution>Sao Paulo</city_of_contribution>
		<lat>-23.400777</lat>
		<long>-46.744995</long>
		<climate_hazard>meteorological</climate_hazard>
		<project_ID>230939140</project_ID>
	</project>
	<project ID="230943009">
		<Name>Eder</Name>
		<Surname>de Oliveira Daniel</Surname>
		<Affiliation></Affiliation>
		<City_of_Institution>Sao Paulo</City_of_Institution>
		<country_001>Brazil</country_001>
		<title_of_project>Eco Park School</title_of_project>
		<credits_for_project>Eder de Oliveira Daniel
Claudine Mendes Silva
Giseli de Oliveira Cardoso</credits_for_project>
		<year_of_project>2021</year_of_project>
		<description_of_project>In 2021, we started an incredible project. We changed an abandoned green area used to discard trash to a pedagogical space for students, complementing the classroom with pedagogy activities.</description_of_project>
		<synopsis_of_project>News spaces of the learning to save the enviroment</synopsis_of_project>
		<keywords_of_project>Eco, Park, School, nature, enviroment</keywords_of_project>
		<duration_of_solution>permanent</duration_of_solution>
		<primary_SDG>Sustainable Cities and Communities</primary_SDG>
		<secondary_SDG>    Quality Education,             </secondary_SDG>
		<country_of_contribution>Brazil</country_of_contribution>
		<city_of_contribution>Sao Paulo</city_of_contribution>
		<lat>-23.401562667885</lat>
		<long>-46.7428185835572</long>
		<climate_hazard>climatological geophysical</climate_hazard>
		<project_ID>230943009</project_ID>
	</project>
	<project ID="231111769">
		<Name>Mohamed</Name>
		<Surname>Yousry</Surname>
		<Affiliation>alexandria_university__egypt</Affiliation>
		<City_of_Institution>Alexandria</City_of_Institution>
		<country_001>Egypt</country_001>
		<title_of_project>Climate Change, Co2 impact and biomaterials, towards Net-Zero emissions.</title_of_project>
		<credits_for_project>Mohmad Assem Hanafy, Mai Mohamed Abdo, Mohamed Yousry Abo-El-Shohood, Marwan Sabry El Ashmawy, Dina Ibrahim Ramadan, Israa Yasser Nasrallah, Arwa AbdelHamid Foda, Yousef Mahmoud Saber, Fatma Mohamed Sleem, Alaa Salah El-Din El-Sawasany, Hend Mohamed Ashraf, Alaa kher manda</credits_for_project>
		<year_of_project>2023</year_of_project>
		<description_of_project>Our civilization is severely affected by climate change, which is shown in different phenomena, especially the CO2 emissions that are affecting the globe and resulting from human activities. As the manufacturing of construction materials in the building industry is considered one of the most significant causes of carbon emissions, the project investigates the potentials of different biomaterial solutions available in Egypt to replace the ordinary materials and develops their manufacturing processes in order to target the projects problem.</description_of_project>
		<synopsis_of_project>Re-designing the materials production process will reshape the future of our planet.</synopsis_of_project>
		<keywords_of_project>CO2,Air Pollution, Biomaterials, Chitin, Hydrogel skeleton</keywords_of_project>
		<duration_of_solution>long</duration_of_solution>
		<primary_SDG>Responsible Consumption and Production</primary_SDG>
		<secondary_SDG>         Industry, Innovation and Infrastructure,  Sustainable Cities and Communities, Responsible Consumption and Production,     </secondary_SDG>
		<country_of_contribution>Egypt</country_of_contribution>
		<city_of_contribution>Alexandria</city_of_contribution>
		<lat>31.2001</lat>
		<long>29.9187</long>
		<climate_hazard>climatological</climate_hazard>
		<project_ID>231111769</project_ID>
	</project>
	<project ID="231834314">
		<Name>Wian</Name>
		<Surname>Jordaan</Surname>
		<Affiliation></Affiliation>
		<City_of_Institution>Pretoria, City of Tshwane</City_of_Institution>
		<country_001>South_Africa</country_001>
		<title_of_project>From the ground up</title_of_project>
		<credits_for_project>Wian Jordaan, AuthorDesigner</credits_for_project>
		<year_of_project>2020</year_of_project>
		<description_of_project>The project is located in Melusi, an informal neighbourhood located in Pretoria, South Africa. The community of Melusi is largely dependent on external networks, resources and investment to support the communitys livelihood. Even though Melusis residents are highly resourceful, the lack of internal resources and support systems limit the communitys adaptive capacity and increase their vulnerability to the hazardous effects of climate change. 

The aim of the project is to provide a bottom-up approach, which enhances existing social, economic and environmental support systems within Melusi, to increase the adaptive capacity and climate change resilience of local residents. The project proposes to create a node of activity and communal facilities to complement the COPCs health clinic and community garden. The intervention will facilitate a process where local residents have the necessary resources, facilities and social support systems to improve their own quality of life and ability to adapt to future change.</description_of_project>
		<synopsis_of_project>Our attempt to address climate change should not be at the expense of the poor and vulnerable.</synopsis_of_project>
		<keywords_of_project>Facilitation, adaptation, process, vulnerability, informal</keywords_of_project>
		<duration_of_solution>permanent</duration_of_solution>
		<primary_SDG>Climate Action</primary_SDG>
		<secondary_SDG>   Good Health and Well-being,    Clean Water and Sanitation,     Sustainable Cities and Communities,      </secondary_SDG>
		<country_of_contribution>South_Africa</country_of_contribution>
		<city_of_contribution>Pretoria</city_of_contribution>
		<lat>-25.723736</lat>
		<long>28.12285</long>
		<climate_hazard>climatological</climate_hazard>
		<project_ID>231834314</project_ID>
	</project>
	<project ID="231911105">
		<Name>Pierre</Name>
		<Surname>Hugo</Surname>
		<Affiliation>university_of_pretoria</Affiliation>
		<City_of_Institution>Tshwane</City_of_Institution>
		<country_001>South_Africa</country_001>
		<title_of_project>Agrarian Haven</title_of_project>
		<credits_for_project>Pierre Hugo, Author</credits_for_project>
		<year_of_project>2022</year_of_project>
		<description_of_project>Ensuring sustainable food security is critical, especially in rapidly urbanising South African cities facing the consequences of climate change. This project aims to address this challenge by building a network that connects a food production facility that focuses on novel food production methods with urban farmers and the thriving informal market. This circular process of production, consumption, and waste ultimately minimises wasted energy and resources. Through adaptively reusing an existing building and opening the structure to public use, it allows communities to connect through shared experiences and spaces. This adaptability is further demonstrated by employing construction methods and materials designed for quick assembly and dismantling, including mass timber, repurposed bricks, and affordable local materials. Ultimately, the agrarian haven integrates food, economy, community, and education to create an empowering platform that will address the need for food security in South African urban cities.</description_of_project>
		<synopsis_of_project>The key to fighting hunger is food sovereignty.</synopsis_of_project>
		<keywords_of_project>Food Security, Urban Farming, Circular Economy, Waste Reduction, Community</keywords_of_project>
		<duration_of_solution>long</duration_of_solution>
		<primary_SDG>Zero Hunger</primary_SDG>
		<secondary_SDG>   Good Health and Well-being,              </secondary_SDG>
		<country_of_contribution>South_Africa</country_of_contribution>
		<city_of_contribution>Pretoria</city_of_contribution>
		<lat>-25.753202</lat>
		<long>28.206578</long>
		<climate_hazard>climatological</climate_hazard>
		<project_ID>231911105</project_ID>
	</project>
	<project ID="231983726">
		<Name>Julia</Name>
		<Surname>Pereira</Surname>
		<Affiliation></Affiliation>
		<City_of_Institution>Sao Carlos - Sao Paulo</City_of_Institution>
		<country_001>Brazil</country_001>
		<title_of_project>A brief history of Napras work and the riverside community way of life</title_of_project>
		<credits_for_project>Julia Martins, NAPRAs president 
Joao Pedro Sisternes, NAPRAs Member
Berenice Simao, Teacher of Sao Carlos do Jamari (Riverside community) 
Marcio Santana de Lima, Resident of Sao Carlos do Jamari (Riverside community)
Ana Sarah Lofti, NAPRAs ex-member
Sandila Alves, Poet from Sao Carlos do Jamari (Riverside community)</credits_for_project>
		<year_of_project>2023</year_of_project>
		<description_of_project>The NAPRA (Nucleus of Support for the Riverside Population of the Amazon) is a private non-profit organization founded in 1993 with the mission of contributing to the conservation of the Amazon Forest and valuing the way of life and culture of the populations that inhabit it.
Our goal is to develop projects together with communities and promote engagement between volunteers and riverside communities, strengthen social participation, visibility of the territory and also contribute to the learning process of students and professionals working in the Amazonian context.
We brought some short testimonies about the work of the institution and the riverside way of life, trying to resume the experience that we share with the communities, to show to all the world the difference in their way of life, consumption and what is it like to be in their territory. We sustain that sometimes the solution for climate change is to look into the traditional peoples who live together with nature.</description_of_project>
		<synopsis_of_project>The solution is hidden in the woods, with the people who live in harmony with the environment.</synopsis_of_project>
		<keywords_of_project>Riverside, ambiental education, ways of living, traditional people, Amazon.</keywords_of_project>
		<duration_of_solution>long</duration_of_solution>
		<primary_SDG>Sustainable Cities and Communities</primary_SDG>
		<secondary_SDG>            Responsible Consumption and Production, Climate Action,    Partnerships to achieve the Goal,</secondary_SDG>
		<country_of_contribution>Brazil</country_of_contribution>
		<city_of_contribution>Porto Velho</city_of_contribution>
		<lat>-8.427546</lat>
		<long>-63.533928</long>
		<climate_hazard>climatological Hydrological</climate_hazard>
		<project_ID>231983726</project_ID>
	</project>
	<project ID="231995872">
		<Name>Lisa</Name>
		<Surname>Safdal</Surname>
		<Affiliation>Chalmers</Affiliation>
		<City_of_Institution>Gothenburg</City_of_Institution>
		<country_001>Sweden</country_001>
		<title_of_project>[ POWER SWITCH ]</title_of_project>
		<credits_for_project>Delaney Davis, Author.
Amalia Athanasia Dimou, Author.
Lisa Safdal, Author.
Axel Uhren, Author.</credits_for_project>
		<year_of_project>2023</year_of_project>
		<description_of_project>In four days, Earth will be hit by a massive geomagnetic storm that will disturb the magnetosphere, knock out the power grid and fry our entire electronic infrastructure. The sun will push out waves of light, exposing the Earths surface to intense radiation. In search for protection from the hazardous rays, humans will be forced to settle underground. The polarity of society changes. New communities are built underground, and the old cities descend into chaos.

The years following the crisis, The prolonged exposure to radiation has caused some... strange... mutations to occur within the plants and animals Upstairs. The humans have learned how to adapt to life Downstairs.</description_of_project>
		<synopsis_of_project>Despite globalization, humanity is unequipped to collaborate to address an issue as impactful as an extreme solar storm-how can we better equip ourselves?</synopsis_of_project>
		<keywords_of_project>Geomagnetic storm, Blackout, Radiation, Life below ground, Social reformation</keywords_of_project>
		<duration_of_solution>long</duration_of_solution>
		<primary_SDG>Life on Land</primary_SDG>
		<secondary_SDG>           Sustainable Cities and Communities, Responsible Consumption and Production,     </secondary_SDG>
		<country_of_contribution>Sweden</country_of_contribution>
		<city_of_contribution>Gothenburg</city_of_contribution>
		<lat>57.74381</lat>
		<long>12.158866</long>
		<climate_hazard>meteorological</climate_hazard>
		<project_ID>231995872</project_ID>
	</project>
	<project ID="232020558">
		<Name>Elena</Name>
		<Surname>Cucchi</Surname>
		<Affiliation>Chalmers</Affiliation>
		<City_of_Institution>Gothenburg</City_of_Institution>
		<country_001>Sweden</country_001>
		<title_of_project>The emergency is now! - Live and play with water</title_of_project>
		<credits_for_project>Elena Cucchi, author
Ebba Gordon Hultsjo, author
Jessica Borjesson, author
Sadia Sharmin, author</credits_for_project>
		<year_of_project>2023</year_of_project>
		<description_of_project>Once upon a place and time, a city was born, Dhaka. Emerging from the fluid fabric of its surroundings, an irascible landscape. Dhaka looked full of life, and in symbiosis with all ecosystems - rivers, floodplains and agricultural fields. Growing up, her relationship with people started to change, but only a few of them recognized her tender landmass. They took away her green spaces, animals, and covered her in concrete and asphalt. Traffic and continuous construction made it impossible for her to breathe. Furious transformations, whether official, private, or spontaneous, succumbed to the regime of a dry ideology. 

Dhaka used to be in love with Ganga, the water, enjoying her playfulness with respect and care. Man did not understand the harmony between the two females and with brutal force he started pushing Ganga away from Dhaka, confining her into strong boundaries. She kept coming back to Dhaka every year with prosperous monsoons, but with the drastic increase of density and sea level rise, the water transformed into aggressive floods spreading fear and diseases. What if Ganga decides to reunite with her beloved Dhaka? What if Ganga returns with a message of hope, teaching children to live in harmony with nature?</description_of_project>
		<synopsis_of_project>We must learn to live with nature to build a resilient future!</synopsis_of_project>
		<keywords_of_project>resilience, storytelling, feminist approach, flooding, climate change</keywords_of_project>
		<duration_of_solution>long</duration_of_solution>
		<primary_SDG>Sustainable Cities and Communities</primary_SDG>
		<secondary_SDG>   Good Health and Well-being,  Gender Equality,        Climate Action,    </secondary_SDG>
		<country_of_contribution>Bangladesh</country_of_contribution>
		<city_of_contribution>Dhaka</city_of_contribution>
		<lat>23.753925</lat>
		<long>90.395898</long>
		<climate_hazard>Hydrological</climate_hazard>
		<project_ID>232020558</project_ID>
	</project>
	<project ID="232144352">
		<Name>Lue-Shane</Name>
		<Surname>Cloete</Surname>
		<Affiliation></Affiliation>
		<City_of_Institution>Pretoria</City_of_Institution>
		<country_001>South_Africa</country_001>
		<title_of_project>Why do we waste so much?</title_of_project>
		<credits_for_project>Lue-Shane Cloete, Author</credits_for_project>
		<year_of_project>2021</year_of_project>
		<description_of_project>This project aims to change the perceptions around waste. Only 6  of South Africans recycle their household waste and this can be attributed to the lack of resources, infrastructure and education that supports ethical waste management practices.  Through an analysis of household waste in a Highrise residential building in Sunnyside, Pretoria, South Africa, this project proposes multiple integrated spatial and infrastructural systems that aims to minimize the ammount of waste sent to landfill. 

Organic waste is broken down in a Bioreactor and transformed into fuel and a nutrient. These products are utilized in the production of hot water and a new clip-on food production facade. Inorganic waste management is underpinned by circular economic principles where products like cardboard, glass and aluminum are sold to recycling depos in the city via waste pickers, which in turn, support their families on the proceeds. 

This project finds that waste is valuable and should be considered as a recourse that can be utilized to supplement the infrastructural needs of impoverished communities in South Africa whilst reducing the ammount of  waste sent to landfill.</description_of_project>
		<synopsis_of_project>Waste is valuable, use it.</synopsis_of_project>
		<keywords_of_project>Bioreactor, Food Facade, Circular Economy,</keywords_of_project>
		<duration_of_solution>permanent</duration_of_solution>
		<primary_SDG>Sustainable Cities and Communities</primary_SDG>
		<secondary_SDG>  Zero Hunger,       Industry, Innovation and Infrastructure,   Responsible Consumption and Production,     </secondary_SDG>
		<country_of_contribution>South_Africa</country_of_contribution>
		<city_of_contribution>Pretoria</city_of_contribution>
		<lat>-25.745945</lat>
		<long>28.188302</long>
		<climate_hazard>meteorological</climate_hazard>
		<project_ID>232144352</project_ID>
	</project>
	<project ID="232203458">
		<Name>Hano</Name>
		<Surname>Venter</Surname>
		<Affiliation></Affiliation>
		<City_of_Institution>Cape Town</City_of_Institution>
		<country_001>South_Africa</country_001>
		<title_of_project>The Melusi Agricultural Community Centre</title_of_project>
		<credits_for_project>Hano Venter, Author</credits_for_project>
		<year_of_project>2020</year_of_project>
		<description_of_project>This intervention attempts to provide Melusi with climate resilient strategies with regards to agriculture and
nutrition. By utilising the existing agricultural and cultural knowledge of the residents of Melusi, the Centre would
attempt to breed new varieties of plants - specifically suited to the Melusi context and climate.
This adaptation would allow the plants to be bred in the present for the inevitable increase in temperature in
the future. Along with supplying Melusi with climatically and contextual appropriate plants and crops, the skills
of the community is to be developed and enhanced.
As a side benefit of the plant breeding programme, the produce grown at the Centre is to be distributed to the
clinic or the Melusi community for consumption or for spreading information on proper nutrition by the Primary Care unit stationed at Melusi.</description_of_project>
		<synopsis_of_project>The key to uncovering climatic resilience lies in the co-development of the community.</synopsis_of_project>
		<keywords_of_project>agro-ecology, communal knowledge sharing, urban agriculture, cultural knowledge, agricultural climate adaptation</keywords_of_project>
		<duration_of_solution>long</duration_of_solution>
		<primary_SDG>Zero Hunger</primary_SDG>
		<secondary_SDG>   Good Health and Well-being,           Life Below Water,   Partnerships to achieve the Goal,</secondary_SDG>
		<country_of_contribution>South_Africa</country_of_contribution>
		<city_of_contribution>Melusi, Pretoria, South Africa</city_of_contribution>
		<lat>-25.723771</lat>
		<long>28.120397</long>
		<climate_hazard>climatological Hydrological biological</climate_hazard>
		<project_ID>232203458</project_ID>
	</project>
	<project ID="232253503">
		<Name>Amany</Name>
		<Surname>Abdel-Aziz</Surname>
		<Affiliation>alexandria_university__egypt</Affiliation>
		<City_of_Institution>Alexanderia</City_of_Institution>
		<country_001>Egypt</country_001>
		<title_of_project>Proposal for Climate-resilient City as solution for water level rise.</title_of_project>
		<credits_for_project>Amany Abdel-Aziz, faculty of engineering, Alexandria university, department of architecture.
Abdelhamid ahmed abdelhamid,faculty of engineering, Alexandria university, department of architecture.
Amr Elsayed Mohamed,faculty of engineering, Alexandria university, department of architecture
Maryam Fouad, faculty of engineering, Alexandria university, department of architecture
Hajar Mohamed Shebl, faculty of engineering, Alexandria university, department of architecture.
Abanoub saadalla , faculty of engineering, Alexandria university, department of architecture.
Abdelrahman khaled said ,faculty of engineering, Alexandria university, department of architecture.
Ashraf Samy Gaber,faculty of engineering, Alexandria university, department of architecture.
Yomna Samy Fathy ,faculty of engineering, Alexandria university, department of architecture.
Rahma Mohammed Sobhy ,faculty of engineering, Alexandria university, department of architecture.
Taiser Badr Mostafa ,faculty of engineering, Alexandria university, department of architecture.</credits_for_project>
		<year_of_project>2023</year_of_project>
		<description_of_project>As the effects of climate change become more apparent, it is essential that we take proactive steps to mitigate their impact. One of the most pressing issues facing cities today is the rise in sea levels caused by melting glaciers and polar ice caps. While traditional methods of resistance can be effective, they are not always sustainable or cost-effective. Instead, a more adaptable approach that focuses on nature-based solutions can generate new opportunities for sustainable growth, green spaces, and improved living conditions.
Our proposal for a climate resilient city centers around the idea of adaptability. Rather than fighting the rising tide, we will work with nature to find solutions that are sustainable and cost-effective. This approach includes creating green spaces, such as parks and community gardens, that can act as natural buffers against rising sea levels. These spaces will also provide opportunities for recreation, socialization, and improved mental health.</description_of_project>
		<synopsis_of_project>To adapt to natural crises through innovative ideas that allows us to thrive in their aftermath.</synopsis_of_project>
		<keywords_of_project>Climate-resilient city, water-level rise, sustainability, efficient community, green infrastructure</keywords_of_project>
		<duration_of_solution>long</duration_of_solution>
		<primary_SDG>Sustainable Cities and Communities</primary_SDG>
		<secondary_SDG>             Climate Action,    </secondary_SDG>
		<country_of_contribution>Egypt</country_of_contribution>
		<city_of_contribution>Alexanderia</city_of_contribution>
		<lat>31.205753</lat>
		<long>29.924526</long>
		<climate_hazard>climatological</climate_hazard>
		<project_ID>232253503</project_ID>
	</project>
	<project ID="232265347">
		<Name>Adrian</Name>
		<Surname>Buffa</Surname>
		<Affiliation></Affiliation>
		<City_of_Institution>Pretoria</City_of_Institution>
		<country_001>South_Africa</country_001>
		<title_of_project>Building community through collaboration</title_of_project>
		<credits_for_project>Adrian Buffa, University of Pretoria</credits_for_project>
		<year_of_project>2020</year_of_project>
		<description_of_project>This investigation takes place in Melusi, a rapidly developing informal settlement to the north west of Pretorias CBD. Its current level of infrastructural deficit and lack of accessible
healthcare facilities contribute to a high degree of vulnerability to internal and external shocks - leading to major health risks for residents. This necessitates an approach to future
development which facilitates the generation of appropriate community-driven responses to these issues. The intention of the proposed intervention is the provision of primary community healthcare infrastructure (including social and spiritual support spaces), which is flexible, and adaptable by community members, in order to respond to shocks such as the Covid-19 pandemic. A layered, incremental intervention is proposed to ensure adaptability and
equitable community-led growth alongside the provision of essential healthcare services.</description_of_project>
		<synopsis_of_project>Community-led collaborative development can help improve the health and well being of vulnerable communities.</synopsis_of_project>
		<keywords_of_project>Incremental, community-led, healthcare, informal settlement, infrastructure</keywords_of_project>
		<duration_of_solution>long</duration_of_solution>
		<primary_SDG>Good Health and Well-being</primary_SDG>
		<secondary_SDG>           Sustainable Cities and Communities,  Climate Action,    Partnerships to achieve the Goal,</secondary_SDG>
		<country_of_contribution>South_Africa</country_of_contribution>
		<city_of_contribution>Pretoria</city_of_contribution>
		<lat>-25.724158</lat>
		<long>28.122767</long>
		<climate_hazard>biological</climate_hazard>
		<project_ID>232265347</project_ID>
	</project>
	<project ID="232318113">
		<Name>Melicia</Name>
		<Surname>van Loggerenberg</Surname>
		<Affiliation></Affiliation>
		<City_of_Institution>Pretoria</City_of_Institution>
		<country_001>South_Africa</country_001>
		<title_of_project>Independence through Interface</title_of_project>
		<credits_for_project>Melicia van Loggerenberg</credits_for_project>
		<year_of_project>2021</year_of_project>
		<description_of_project>Finding out what really happens after a building is finished doesnt seem to be anyones job... (Feireiss and Bouman, 2011)

The covid pandemic has brought about a period of release where new ways of living has resulted in an economic crisis. If our aim is to move towards regenerative thinking, then we need to redesign the current system to one that projects a positive future narrative where buildings are able to react to changing conditions. In the development of this scheme, I attempted to follow a more deep-seated, personal approach to Green building. This building practice required an understanding of the social, physical and economic diversity of a place. It adopted a notion of imperfect knowledge that would enable architectural interventions to serve as an evolving prototype where built environment professionals can begin to better understand a buildings responsibility in relation to its urban surroundings over time.

These theories were put to the test in a readaptation scheme where an empty office building was transformed into a mixed-use residential building. The aim of the readapting focused on making the structure more responsive to the contextual climate. This was achieved by turning the two main occupiable zones of the building to face true North and in doing so allow the North Eastern wind to passively cool the structure. The addition of secondary hallways would improve the extent of passive ventilation.

Furthermore, green pockets and wet balconies were positioned on the main ventilation axes, cooling the air before it moves through the building.

And finally the tectonic frame that wraps the structure would respond visually to the changes in atmospheric temperatures. This would become a visual warning, to both the building residents as well as the whole of Sunny Side, that outside temperatures are becoming hazardous.</description_of_project>
		<synopsis_of_project>I am of the belief that a more deep-seated personal approach to Green building practices holds the key to involving smaller local actors in addressing bigger systemic issues.</synopsis_of_project>
		<keywords_of_project>Interface, Independence, Micro-climates, Adaptable, Ownership</keywords_of_project>
		<duration_of_solution>long</duration_of_solution>
		<primary_SDG>Sustainable Cities and Communities</primary_SDG>
		<secondary_SDG>             Climate Action,    </secondary_SDG>
		<country_of_contribution>South_Africa</country_of_contribution>
		<city_of_contribution>Pretoria</city_of_contribution>
		<lat>-25.751855</lat>
		<long>28.204962</long>
		<climate_hazard>meteorological</climate_hazard>
		<project_ID>232318113</project_ID>
	</project>
	<project ID="232322002">
		<Name>Nouran</Name>
		<Surname>Naguib</Surname>
		<Affiliation>alexandria_university__egypt</Affiliation>
		<City_of_Institution>Alexandria</City_of_Institution>
		<country_001>Egypt</country_001>
		<title_of_project>climate change sea level rise</title_of_project>
		<credits_for_project>Nouran Mohamed Naguib, Assistant Lecturer, supervisor
Ebtihal El-sayed Meliha, student
Menatallah Gaber Mostafa, student
Menna Ali Khamis, student
Abdelrahman El Sayed, student
Mennatallah Nabil Hussein, student
Abeer Atia Gaber, student
Mayar Ehab Saad, Student
Kareem Mohamed El-Sayed, student
Mohamed Gamal Abd El-Fatah, student
Abdel-rahman Zakaria, student</credits_for_project>
		<year_of_project>2023</year_of_project>
		<description_of_project>The climate change phenomenon  has a negative impact on various environments. The problems resulting from this phenomenon were presented, such as sea level rise, drought, loss of biodiversity, and high marine temperatures. The team delved into the problem of sea level rise associated with the seas and oceans, which plays a fundamental role In reducing global greenhouse gas emissions and stabilizing the Earths climate, as a result of the high temperatures associated with the phenomenon of climate change, melting of glaciers occurs and expansion of sea and ocean waters, so the level rises to affect negatively in the form of floods in other regions, which causes damage to those regions. After an interview with a group of specialized academics, the method of dealing with the problem and the available local solutions in the Delta of Egypt were discussed, specifically in the Kafr El-Sheikh governorate, whose population is seriously exposed to the threat of rising sea levels, like other governorates of the northern coast of Egypt, as a result of the rise in water levels, its creep from the shore and the penetration of its salinity. With soil spoil crops, damage homes, and disrupt interests. Therefore, the primitive methods used by the local population were put forward and were adopted and developed later, such as the use of double-layered wicker dams on the beaches to confine the sand between them, thus forming sustainable environmentally friendly dams, and then presenting the positive results of those dams in resolving the crisis. The project was well received by the state, to be partnered with the United Nations to develop it to extend 69 km along the northern coast, with the aim of saving 17 million people.
This example was shown to be a model among the many models in the world that provide effective solutions to save the planet.</description_of_project>
		<synopsis_of_project>We have one planet, lets swim towards saving it.</synopsis_of_project>
		<keywords_of_project>Climate Action, Sea level rise, Resilience, Gender Equality, Local Communities</keywords_of_project>
		<duration_of_solution>long</duration_of_solution>
		<primary_SDG>Sustainable Cities and Communities</primary_SDG>
		<secondary_SDG>     Gender Equality,   Decent Work and Economic Growth,     Climate Action,    </secondary_SDG>
		<country_of_contribution>Egypt</country_of_contribution>
		<city_of_contribution>Kafr el-sheikh</city_of_contribution>
		<lat>31.41515</lat>
		<long>30.876861</long>
		<climate_hazard>climatological</climate_hazard>
		<project_ID>232322002</project_ID>
	</project>
	<project ID="232327065">
		<Name>Jala</Name>
		<Surname>Hemdan</Surname>
		<Affiliation>alexandria_university__egypt</Affiliation>
		<City_of_Institution>Alexandria</City_of_Institution>
		<country_001>Egypt</country_001>
		<title_of_project>Urban Heat Island Effect</title_of_project>
		<credits_for_project>Belal Ahmed , Alexandria University
Omnia Zaghloul , Alexandria University
Sama Ahmed, Alexandria University
Ashrakat Walid, Alexandria University
Hannah Mansour , Alexandria University
Sara Samir, Alexandria University
Hania Osama , Alexandria University
Aya Ossama , Alexandria University
Mohamed El-Mallah, Alexandria University
Sohaila Salah, Alexandria University</credits_for_project>
		<year_of_project>2022</year_of_project>
		<description_of_project>An urban heat island is an urban area that is significantly warmer than its surrounding rural areas due to human activities. The temperature difference Is usually larger at night than during the day, and is most apparent when Winds are weak. UHI is most noticeable during the summer. It occurs when cities replace natural land cover with structures such as buildings, roads, and other infrastructure that absorb and re-emit the suns heat more than natural landscapes such as Forests and water Bodies. The urban heat island effect represents an important environmental problem facing all large urban centers. As a result this serious issue must be taken into consideration through various solutions according to the latest movements towards saving the planet from climate change.</description_of_project>
		<synopsis_of_project>The urban heat island effect represents an important environmental problem facing all large urban centers.</synopsis_of_project>
		<keywords_of_project>urban heat island, climate, sustainability, treatment, flood</keywords_of_project>
		<duration_of_solution>long</duration_of_solution>
		<primary_SDG>Sustainable Cities and Communities</primary_SDG>
		<secondary_SDG>             Climate Action,  Life on Land,  </secondary_SDG>
		<country_of_contribution>Egypt</country_of_contribution>
		<city_of_contribution>Alexandria</city_of_contribution>
		<lat>31.211921</lat>
		<long>30.167536</long>
		<climate_hazard>Hydrological</climate_hazard>
		<project_ID>232327065</project_ID>
	</project>
	<project ID="232340040">
		<Name>Laura</Name>
		<Surname>Estrada</Surname>
		<Affiliation>Chalmers</Affiliation>
		<City_of_Institution>Gothenburg</City_of_Institution>
		<country_001>Sweden</country_001>
		<title_of_project>Speculative flooding scenario in Santa Monica Pier</title_of_project>
		<credits_for_project>Adam Back Thoren, author
Gwendolyn Bauer, author
Laura Estrada, author
Ida Ylenfors, author</credits_for_project>
		<year_of_project>2022</year_of_project>
		<description_of_project>The poster presents a possible future scenario where Santa Monica, California is flooded due to the sea level rising and the overexploitation of sand as a construction resource. In this scenario, Three different approaches compete to tackle the challenge through either technology, environmental innovation or social resilience; these approximations see the key to a resilience design according to thier particular interests and lack an holistic perspective of the situation, so the municipality decides to combine the three proposals. Nonetheless, the threath of an inminate cathastrofic earthquake makes us question in this instalation if it is truly sustainable to put all these efforts and resources to mantain resilience in such a vulnerable location.</description_of_project>
		<synopsis_of_project>Resilience design needs to be an adaptive, there is no final concept, no final solution, we need each other to evolve our plans and thrive together.</synopsis_of_project>
		<keywords_of_project>resilience, flooding, sustainability, cooperation, design</keywords_of_project>
		<duration_of_solution>short</duration_of_solution>
		<primary_SDG>Sustainable Cities and Communities</primary_SDG>
		<secondary_SDG>             Climate Action,  Life on Land,  </secondary_SDG>
		<country_of_contribution>United_States</country_of_contribution>
		<city_of_contribution>Santa Monica</city_of_contribution>
		<lat>34.006856</lat>
		<long>-118.496966</long>
		<climate_hazard>Hydrological</climate_hazard>
		<project_ID>232340040</project_ID>
	</project>
	<project ID="232363273">
		<Name>Yasmin</Name>
		<Surname>Anefalos de Oliveira</Surname>
		<Affiliation>other</Affiliation>
		<City_of_Institution>Sao Paulo</City_of_Institution>
		<country_001>Brazil</country_001>
		<title_of_project>Territory of Interest of Culture and Landscape Jaragua-Perus-Anhanguera - Sao Paulo, Brazil</title_of_project>
		<credits_for_project>Euler Sandeville Jr., Center for Landscape Studies, Senior Professor at the University of Sao Paulo
Yasmin Anefalos de Oliveira, Center for Landscape Studies, University of Sao Paulo
Valdirene Ijano, Center for Landscape Studies, University of Sao Paulo
Natalia Teixeira Lopes da Costa, Center for Landscape Studies, University of Sao Paulo
Patricia Siqueira Melo Center for Landscape Studies, University of Sao Paulo and Integrated Center for Youth and Adult Education Perus I
Gabriela Yi Zhu Chan, Center for Landscape Studies, University of Sao Paulo
Regina Celia Soares Bortoto, Coruja Colective, Paulista Heritage Education Network
Marcio Antonio Melhado Bezerra, Coruja Colective, Paulo Freire Colective
Mario Sergio Bortoto, Coruja Colective, Paulista Heritage Education Network
Maria Helena Bertolini Bezerra, Projeto Coruja, Paulo Freire Collective
Pedro Augusto Bertolini Bezerra, University of Sao Paulo, EMEF CEU - Municipal Elementary School of the Unified Educational Center Perus
Gisele Costa, member of Parque Anhanguera Management Council Management 20222024, Schedules
Juliana Costa (narration)
Cleiton Ferreira, Quilombaque Cultural Community, Agendas
Jose Queiroz, Quilombaque Cultural Community (Soro, in memorian)
Sirlei Bertolini, member of Representative on the Council for the Environment and Sustainability Subprefecture Pirituba Jaragua
Suerda Deboa, Morada Jaragua Collective and Cultural Space, member of Representative on the Council for the Environment and Sustainability Subprefecture Pirituba Jaragua

All authors integrate the movement for the Territory of Interest of Culture and Landscape Jaragua-Perus-Anhanguera and the Free and Collaborative University project.</credits_for_project>
		<year_of_project>2023</year_of_project>
		<description_of_project>We are a Brazilian collective acting in the territory Jaragua-Perus-Anhanguera, three peripheral districts in the northwest region of the city of Sao Paulo, which integrate the biosphere reserve of the municipality. Since 2011, the movement for the Reappropriation of the Perus Cement Factory, the Quilombaque Cultural Community, the Coruja collective, in continuity to the Queixada labor movement, with the Center for Landscape Studies at FAU-USP, develop with other social actors the Free and Collaborative University project, integrating local and academic knowledge under the principles of nonviolent resistance and permanent firmness. We created in the 2014 Master Plan an innovative urbanistic instrument called "Territory of Interest of Culture and Landscape Jaragua-Perus-Anhanguera", which integrates education, culture and environment and is based on social participation and the construction of knowledge for a more supportive and sustainable city. We work with educational, cultural and popular museology projects, seeking local income generation and socio-environmental solutions responsive to climate and urban changes in the preservation of the natural and cultural heritage and of the values of the landscape as a collective patrimony. There is a lot to do and we are doing it. Join us!</description_of_project>
		<synopsis_of_project>To hope for the future acting collaboratively in the present for a fairer and more sustainable environment.</synopsis_of_project>
		<keywords_of_project>Environment, Education, Culture, Landscape, Social Participation</keywords_of_project>
		<duration_of_solution>long</duration_of_solution>
		<primary_SDG>Sustainable Cities and Communities</primary_SDG>
		<secondary_SDG>    Quality Education,    Decent Work and Economic Growth,  Reduced Inequality,       </secondary_SDG>
		<country_of_contribution>Brazil</country_of_contribution>
		<city_of_contribution>Sao Paulo</city_of_contribution>
		<lat>-23.41812</lat>
		<long>-46.766466</long>
		<climate_hazard>Hydrological</climate_hazard>
		<project_ID>232363273</project_ID>
	</project>
	<project ID="232376874">
		<Name>Adrienne</Name>
		<Surname>MacDonald</Surname>
		<Affiliation>university_of_pretoria</Affiliation>
		<City_of_Institution>Pretoria</City_of_Institution>
		<country_001>South_Africa</country_001>
		<title_of_project>Public Node Development Through Water Infrastructure</title_of_project>
		<credits_for_project>Mitchell Austin
Susanna Swanepoel
Adrienne MacDonald</credits_for_project>
		<year_of_project>2022</year_of_project>
		<description_of_project>The aim of this project was to understand the vulnerability of
the local community and develop an adaptation
response strategy using the public realm as a structuring
device.
This project explores the complex roles of spatial nodes
and water supply in Melusi (an informal settlement in
Tshwane, South Africa), through an examination of its contextual
setting and spatial characteristics.
Through a series of mapping exercises, and an
understanding of risk in conjunction with "informality"
and "public space," the possible vulnerabilities and
opportunities within Melusi are unpacked.
From this, arises the potential of an intimate relationship
between spatial nodes, and water supply infrastructure.
The project reflect on the possible socio-economic effects of
such an intervention, all the while learning from the
locals "Melusian" way of life.</description_of_project>
		<synopsis_of_project>Resilient informal settlements can utilise small infrastructural inputs to mitigate climate change</synopsis_of_project>
		<keywords_of_project>Climate change, Resilience, Nodes, Water infrastructure, Vulnerability</keywords_of_project>
		<duration_of_solution>short</duration_of_solution>
		<primary_SDG> Clean Water and Sanitation</primary_SDG>
		<secondary_SDG>           Sustainable Cities and Communities,      </secondary_SDG>
		<country_of_contribution>South_Africa</country_of_contribution>
		<city_of_contribution>Tswhane</city_of_contribution>
		<lat>-25.723132</lat>
		<long>28.11676</long>
		<climate_hazard>climatological</climate_hazard>
		<project_ID>232376874</project_ID>
	</project>
	<project ID="232421110">
		<Name>Veronica</Name>
		<Surname>Garcia Donoso</Surname>
		<Affiliation>other</Affiliation>
		<City_of_Institution>I am a Professor at the Federal University of Santa Maria, Cachoeira do Sul-RS (Brazil). Currently experienced researcher living in Monchengladbach, Germany.</City_of_Institution>
		<country_001>Brazil</country_001>
		<title_of_project>Rainforest importance for climate change and the relevance of ecological planning for cities within forest areas</title_of_project>
		<credits_for_project>Prof. Dr. Veronica Garcia Donoso, Professor at the Federal University of Santa Maria (UFSM), Brazil; Experienced Researcher, Alexander von Humboldt Foundation, Germany.</credits_for_project>
		<year_of_project>2023</year_of_project>
		<description_of_project>The Amazon region is globally crucial for the biodiversity and climate system. Many studies have suggested that the global warming and deforestation combined can push the Amazon rainforest beyond critical limits. New technologies and satellite images have made it possible to monitor forest cover. However, the sequence of actions needs political, economic and cultural global support. From 1985 to 2021, the forest area in the Brazilian Amazon reduced 44,1 Mha; the loss of forest is related with the increase of pasture areas for livestock, with increased from around 37 Mha in the same period. Particularly intense deforestation is occurring in the state of Rondonia, in southern Brazil, with the clearance of land for livestock, agriculture and urban areas. With the change in land use and the reduced forest areas, rain is now falling in longer massive bursts and floodings are reaching records. Cities could place a crucial role in the maintenance and awareness of the Amazon biodiversity and the climate mitigation importance. Also, awareness of the importance of the forest has to be strengthened through education, especially in the Amazon region, its communities and cities.</description_of_project>
		<synopsis_of_project></synopsis_of_project>
		<keywords_of_project>Amazon, Rondonia, Deforestation, Climate Change, Cities.</keywords_of_project>
		<duration_of_solution>long</duration_of_solution>
		<primary_SDG>Sustainable Cities and Communities</primary_SDG>
		<secondary_SDG>             Climate Action,    </secondary_SDG>
		<country_of_contribution>Brazil</country_of_contribution>
		<city_of_contribution>Porto Velho-RO</city_of_contribution>
		<lat>-8.752724</lat>
		<long>-63.887159</long>
		<climate_hazard>climatological Hydrological</climate_hazard>
		<project_ID>232421110</project_ID>
	</project>
	<project ID="232442630">
		<Name>Pia Alejandra</Name>
		<Surname>Galvez Lindegaard</Surname>
		<Affiliation>other</Affiliation>
		<City_of_Institution>Complutense University of Madrid</City_of_Institution>
		<country_001>Spain</country_001>
		<title_of_project>Annotations</title_of_project>
		<credits_for_project>Pia Galvez, Faculty of Fine Arts Complutense University of Madrid</credits_for_project>
		<year_of_project>2023</year_of_project>
		<description_of_project>I am narrating what I normally observe. I am reporting some events which got my attention and are associated to different biological or hydrological hazards.
Even if they could be related or not to my daily life, they are relevant for my ongoing artistic research.</description_of_project>
		<synopsis_of_project>Focus on what yo can do: positive impacts and behavioral changes.</synopsis_of_project>
		<keywords_of_project>artistic research, research-creation, environmental arts, ocean, water</keywords_of_project>
		<duration_of_solution>short long permanent</duration_of_solution>
		<primary_SDG>Climate Action</primary_SDG>
		<secondary_SDG>           Sustainable Cities and Communities,   Life Below Water, Life on Land,  </secondary_SDG>
		<country_of_contribution>Spain</country_of_contribution>
		<city_of_contribution>Madrid</city_of_contribution>
		<lat>40.440264</lat>
		<long>-3.733861</long>
		<climate_hazard>Hydrological biological</climate_hazard>
		<project_ID>232442630</project_ID>
	</project>
	<project ID="232473032">
		<Name>Tessa</Name>
		<Surname>van Mourik</Surname>
		<Affiliation>tu_delft__the_netherlands</Affiliation>
		<City_of_Institution>Delft</City_of_Institution>
		<country_001>Netherlands</country_001>
		<title_of_project>Symbiotic Urban Movement</title_of_project>
		<credits_for_project>Annemiek Braunius, Transition Expert SUM 
Nando Versteeg, Transition Expert SUM
Nikki de Zeeuw, Transition Expert SUM
Andy van den Dobbelsteen, Sustainability Project Coordinator</credits_for_project>
		<year_of_project>2022</year_of_project>
		<description_of_project>Symbiotic Urban Movement (SUM) was the Solar Decathlon team of TU Delft. The students developed net- positive energy strategies targeting 847.000 underperforming rental flats in the Netherlands. SUMs ambition was to achieve a mutually beneficial relationship between the user, the community, and the environment.

The top-up apartments are prefabricated, modular and biobased. They can be lifted onto the existing building and become the powerplant of the entire block, covered with solar panels on roof and facade. They can also collect rainwater for toilet flushing and plants. In reverse, the existing building provides the foundation for the new apartments. Symbiosis!</description_of_project>
		<synopsis_of_project>With our tenement flat repurposing strategy we would like to make a world where diversity, innovation and social interaction are stimulated. Where clever design solutions can tackle social, economic and environmental challenges.</synopsis_of_project>
		<keywords_of_project>Teamwork, innovation, multidiscplinary, sustainable design, future</keywords_of_project>
		<duration_of_solution>long</duration_of_solution>
		<primary_SDG>Sustainable Cities and Communities</primary_SDG>
		<secondary_SDG>             Climate Action,    </secondary_SDG>
		<country_of_contribution>Netherlands</country_of_contribution>
		<city_of_contribution>Delft</city_of_contribution>
		<lat>52.005786</lat>
		<long>4.370418</long>
		<climate_hazard>meteorological climatological</climate_hazard>
		<project_ID>232473032</project_ID>
	</project>
</data-set>
